Hafize,B-PERSON
Gaye,I-PERSON
Erkan,I-PERSON
-,O
Ms.,O
Erkan,B-PERSON
",",O
40,B-DATE
",",O
is,O
the,O
President,B-TITLE
of,O
First,B-ORG
Republic,I-ORG
Bank,I-ORG
(,O
``,O
First,B-ORG
Republic,I-ORG
'',O
),O
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
becoming,O
President,B-TITLE
in,O
2017,B-DATE
",",O
she,O
served,O
as,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Investment,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
and,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Deposit,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
First,B-ORG
Republic,I-ORG
from,O
January,B-DATE
2016,I-DATE
to,I-DATE
May,I-DATE
2017,I-DATE
",",O
as,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Investment,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
from,O
September,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
December,I-DATE
2015,I-DATE
and,O
as,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Investment,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
and,O
Co-Chief,B-TITLE
Risk,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
from,O
June,B-DATE
2014,I-DATE
to,I-DATE
August,I-DATE
2015,I-DATE
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
First,B-ORG
Republic,I-ORG
",",O
she,O
held,O
the,O
position,O
of,O
Managing,B-TITLE
Director,I-TITLE
and,O
Head,B-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Financial,I-TITLE
Institutions,I-TITLE
Group,I-TITLE
Strategies,I-TITLE
at,O
Goldman,B-ORG
Sachs,I-ORG
",",O
where,O
she,O
worked,O
in,O
roles,O
of,O
increasing,O
responsibility,O
for,O
nearly,B-DATE
a,I-DATE
decade,I-DATE
",",O
advising,O
boards,O
and,O
executive,O
management,O
of,O
large,O
U.S.,O
banks,O
and,O
insurance,O
companies,O
.,O
,
Ms.,O
Erkan,B-PERSON
holds,O
a,O
B.Sc,O
.,O
from,O
Bogazici,B-ORG
University,I-ORG
(,O
Turkey,B-GPE
),O
and,O
a,O
Ph.D.,O
from,O
Princeton,B-ORG
University,I-ORG
.,O
,
Key,O
Skills,O
:,O
finance,O
",",O
strategic,O
planning,O
",",O
risk,O
management,O
",",O
brand,O
management,O
",",O
data,O
and,O
analytics,O
and,O
strategic,O
transactions,O
.,O
,
Roger,B-PERSON
N.,I-PERSON
Farah,I-PERSON
-,O
Mr.,O
Farah,B-PERSON
",",O
66,B-DATE
",",O
became,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Tiffany,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
in,O
March,B-DATE
2017,I-DATE
and,O
was,O
elected,O
Chairman,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Board,B-ORG
in,O
October,B-DATE
2017,I-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
served,O
as,O
the,O
Co-CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Tory,B-ORG
Burch,I-ORG
LLC,I-ORG
from,O
2014,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
March,I-DATE
2017,I-DATE
",",O
when,O
he,O
transitioned,O
to,O
the,O
role,O
of,O
Executive,B-TITLE
Director,I-TITLE
",",O
which,O
he,O
held,O
through,O
December,B-DATE
2017,I-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
also,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
member,O
of,O
the,O
Board,O
of,O
Directors,O
of,O
Tory,B-ORG
Burch,I-ORG
LLC,I-ORG
from,O
2014,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2017,I-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Farah,B-PERSON
served,O
as,O
President,B-TITLE
and,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Operating,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
Ralph,B-ORG
Lauren,I-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
from,O
2000,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2013,I-DATE
and,O
as,O
Executive,B-TITLE
Vice,I-TITLE
Chairman,I-TITLE
from,O
November,B-DATE
2013,I-DATE
to,I-DATE
May,I-DATE
2014,I-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
was,O
a,O
member,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Board,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Directors,I-ORG
of,O
Ralph,B-ORG
Lauren,I-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
from,O
2000,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2014,I-DATE
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
joining,O
Ralph,B-ORG
Lauren,I-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
",",O
he,O
served,O
as,O
Chairman,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Board,B-ORG
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Venator,B-ORG
Group,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
(,O
now,O
Foot,B-ORG
Locker,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
),O
",",O
as,O
President,B-TITLE
and,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Operating,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
R.H.,B-ORG
Macy,I-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
and,O
as,O
Chairman,B-TITLE
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Federated,B-ORG
Merchandising,I-ORG
Services,I-ORG
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Farah,B-PERSON
currently,O
serves,O
on,O
the,O
Board,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Directors,I-ORG
of,O
The,B-ORG
Progressive,I-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
and,O
CVS,B-ORG
Health,I-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
",",O
and,O
as,O
a,O
non-management,B-TITLE
director,I-TITLE
of,O
Metro,B-ORG
Bank,I-ORG
PLC,I-ORG
.,O
,
He,O
also,O
served,O
on,O
the,O
Board,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Directors,I-ORG
of,O
the,O
following,O
public,O
company,O
during,O
the,O
past,B-DATE
five,I-DATE
years,I-DATE
:,O
Aetna,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
(,O
which,O
was,O
acquired,O
by,O
CVS,B-ORG
Health,I-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
in,O
November,B-DATE
2018,I-DATE
),O
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Farah,B-PERSON
holds,O
a,O
B.S,B-PRODUCT
.,O
,
Key,O
Skills,O
:,O
luxury,O
brand,O
management,O
",",O
global,O
management,O
",",O
marketing,O
and,O
product,O
development,O
.,O
,
Jane,B-PERSON
Hertzmark,I-PERSON
Hudis,I-PERSON
-,O
Ms.,O
Hertzmark,B-PERSON
Hudis,I-PERSON
",",O
59,B-DATE
",",O
is,O
the,O
Group,B-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
of,O
The,B-ORG
Estée,I-ORG
Lauder,I-ORG
Companies,I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
(,O
``,O
Estée,B-ORG
Lauder,I-ORG
'',O
),O
.,O
,
In,O
this,O
role,O
",",O
in,O
which,O
she,O
has,O
served,O
since,O
January,B-DATE
2015,I-DATE
",",O
she,O
is,O
responsible,O
for,O
leading,O
the,O
company,O
's,O
Estée,B-ORG
Lauder,I-ORG
",",O
La,B-ORG
Mer,I-ORG
",",O
Bobbi,B-ORG
Brown,I-ORG
",",O
AERIN,B-ORG
",",O
Darphin,B-ORG
",",O
Origins,B-ORG
",",O
Aveda,B-ORG
and,O
Bumble,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
bumble,I-ORG
brands,O
globally,O
.,O
,
From,O
2009,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2014,I-DATE
",",O
Ms.,O
Hertzmark,B-PERSON
Hudis,I-PERSON
served,O
as,O
Global,B-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Estée,B-ORG
Lauder,I-ORG
brand,O
.,O
,
Since,O
joining,O
Estée,B-ORG
Lauder,I-ORG
in,O
1986,B-DATE
",",O
she,O
has,O
served,O
in,O
management,O
positions,O
of,O
increasing,O
responsibility,O
",",O
including,O
as,O
President,B-TITLE
of,O
Origins,B-ORG
and,O
President,B-TITLE
of,O
BeautyBank,B-ORG
",",O
a,O
brand,O
innovation,O
think,O
tank,O
she,O
co-founded,O
in,O
2003,B-DATE
.,O
,
Ms.,O
Hertzmark,B-PERSON
Hudis,B-PERSON
serves,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Fashion,B-ORG
Institute,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Technology,I-ORG
(,O
``,O
FIT,B-ORG
'',O
),O
Foundation,B-ORG
as,O
well,O
as,O
a,O
member,B-TITLE
of,O
FIT,B-ORG
's,O
executive,B-TITLE
committee,I-TITLE
of,O
the,O
cosmetics,O
and,O
fragrance,O
marketing,O
and,O
management,O
graduate,O
program,O
.,O
,
She,O
holds,O
a,O
B.A,B-PRODUCT
.,O
from,O
Vassar,B-ORG
College,I-ORG
and,O
an,O
M.B.A.,B-PRODUCT
from,O
Columbia,B-ORG
Business,I-ORG
School,I-ORG
.,O
,
Key,O
Skills,O
:,O
retail,O
and,O
brand,O
management,O
",",O
global,O
management,O
",",O
strategic,O
planning,O
",",O
product,O
innovation,O
and,O
digital,O
marketing,O
.,O
,
Abby,B-PERSON
F.,I-PERSON
Kohnstamm,I-PERSON
-,O
Ms.,O
Kohnstamm,B-PERSON
",",O
65,B-DATE
",",O
became,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Tiffany,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
in,O
2001,B-DATE
.,O
,
In,O
this,O
role,O
",",O
she,O
managed,O
Pitney,B-ORG
Bowes,I-ORG
's,O
worldwide,O
marketing,O
and,O
communications,O
",",O
pitneybowes.com,O
",",O
as,O
well,O
as,O
citizenship,O
and,O
philanthropy,O
for,O
Pitney,B-ORG
Bowes,I-ORG
.,O
,
Before,O
joining,O
Pitney,B-ORG
Bowes,I-ORG
",",O
Ms.,O
Kohnstamm,B-PERSON
was,O
the,O
President,B-TITLE
and,O
founder,B-TITLE
of,O
Abby,B-ORG
F.,I-ORG
Kohnstamm,I-ORG
&,I-ORG
Associates,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
marketing,O
and,O
consulting,O
firm,O
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
establishing,O
her,O
company,O
in,O
2006,B-DATE
",",O
Ms.,O
Kohnstamm,B-PERSON
served,O
as,O
Senior,B-TITLE
Vice,I-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
",",I-TITLE
Marketing,I-TITLE
(,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Marketing,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
),O
of,O
IBM,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
from,O
1993,B-DATE
through,I-DATE
2005,I-DATE
.,O
,
In,O
that,O
capacity,O
",",O
she,O
had,O
overall,O
responsibility,O
for,O
all,O
aspects,O
of,O
marketing,O
and,O
corporate,O
philanthropy,O
across,O
IBM,B-ORG
on,O
a,O
global,O
basis,O
.,O
,
Before,O
joining,O
IBM,B-ORG
",",O
Ms.,O
Kohnstamm,B-PERSON
held,O
a,O
number,O
of,O
senior,B-TITLE
marketing,I-TITLE
positions,I-TITLE
at,O
American,B-ORG
Express,I-ORG
from,O
1979,B-DATE
through,I-DATE
1993,I-DATE
.,O
,
Ms.,O
Kohnstamm,B-PERSON
is,O
a,O
member,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Board,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Directors,I-ORG
of,O
the,O
Roundabout,B-ORG
Theatre,I-ORG
Company,I-ORG
and,O
Sanctuary,B-ORG
for,I-ORG
Families,I-ORG
",",O
as,O
well,O
as,O
Trustee,B-TITLE
Emeritus,I-TITLE
of,O
Tufts,B-ORG
University,I-ORG
,
.,O
She,O
holds,O
a,O
B.A,B-PRODUCT
.,O
from,O
Tufts,B-ORG
University,I-ORG
",",O
an,O
M.A,B-PRODUCT
.,O
in,O
Education,O
from,O
New,B-ORG
York,I-ORG
University,I-ORG
and,O
an,O
M.B.A.,B-PRODUCT
from,O
New,B-ORG
York,I-ORG
University,I-ORG
Stern,I-ORG
School,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Business,I-ORG
.,O
,
Key,O
Skills,O
:,O
brand,O
management,O
",",O
global,O
management,O
",",O
strategic,O
planning,O
",",O
product,O
development,O
",",O
digital,O
marketing,O
and,O
e-commerce,O
.,O
,
James,B-PERSON
E.,I-PERSON
Lillie,I-PERSON
-,O
Mr.,O
Lillie,B-PERSON
",",O
57,B-DATE
",",O
became,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Tiffany,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
in,O
March,B-DATE
2017,I-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
is,O
the,O
Vice,B-TITLE
Chairman,I-TITLE
of,O
Mariposa,B-ORG
Capital,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
private,O
investment,O
office,O
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
April,B-DATE
2019,I-DATE
",",O
he,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
consultant,B-TITLE
for,O
Newell,B-ORG
Brands,I-ORG
",",O
which,O
acquired,O
Jarden,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
in,O
April,B-DATE
2016,I-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
held,O
senior,B-TITLE
positions,I-TITLE
at,O
Jarden,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
from,O
2003,B-DATE
through,O
the,O
aforementioned,O
acquisition,O
of,O
the,O
company,O
",",O
including,O
as,O
President,B-TITLE
and,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Operating,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
and,O
",",O
beginning,O
in,O
2011,B-DATE
",",O
CEO,B-TITLE
.,O
,
He,O
also,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
member,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Board,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Directors,I-ORG
of,O
Jarden,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
from,O
2011,B-DATE
until,O
the,O
aforementioned,O
acquisition,O
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
joining,O
Jarden,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
",",O
Mr.,O
Lillie,B-PERSON
served,O
as,O
Executive,B-TITLE
Vice,I-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Operations,I-TITLE
at,O
Moore,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
Limited,I-ORG
and,O
held,O
several,O
senior,O
level,O
management,O
positions,O
at,O
portfolio,O
companies,O
of,O
Kohlberg,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
Kravis,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Roberts,I-ORG
&,I-ORG
Company,I-ORG
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Lillie,B-PERSON
serves,O
on,O
the,O
Board,B-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Directors,I-TITLE
of,O
J2,B-ORG
Acquisition,I-ORG
Limited,I-ORG
and,O
Nomad,B-ORG
Foods,I-ORG
Limited,I-ORG
",",O
and,O
previously,O
served,O
on,O
the,O
Board,B-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Directors,I-TITLE
of,O
Radio,B-ORG
Prisa,I-ORG
in,O
Spain,B-GPE
and,O
the,O
US-China,B-ORG
Business,I-ORG
Council,I-ORG
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Lillie,B-PERSON
holds,O
a,O
B.A,B-PRODUCT
.,O
from,O
the,O
University,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Wisconsin,I-ORG
.,O
,
Key,O
Skills,O
:,O
global,O
management,O
",",O
strategic,O
planning,O
",",O
finance,O
",",O
product,O
innovation,O
and,O
business,O
process,O
optimization,O
.,O
,
William,B-PERSON
A.,I-PERSON
Shutzer,I-PERSON
-,O
Mr.,O
Shutzer,B-PERSON
",",O
72,B-DATE
",",O
became,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Tiffany,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
in,O
1984,B-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
has,O
been,O
a,O
Senior,B-TITLE
Managing,I-TITLE
Director,I-TITLE
of,O
Evercore,B-ORG
Partners,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
financial,O
advisory,O
and,O
private,O
equity,O
firm,O
",",O
since,O
2004,B-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
previously,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
Managing,B-TITLE
Director,I-TITLE
of,O
Lehman,B-ORG
Brothers,I-ORG
from,O
2000,B-DATE
through,I-DATE
2003,I-DATE
",",O
a,O
Partner,B-TITLE
in,O
Thomas,B-ORG
Weisel,I-ORG
Partners,I-ORG
LLC,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
merchant,O
banking,O
firm,O
",",O
from,O
1999,B-DATE
through,I-DATE
2000,I-DATE
",",O
as,O
Executive,B-TITLE
Vice,I-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
of,O
ING,B-ORG
Baring,I-ORG
Furman,I-ORG
Selz,I-ORG
LLC,I-ORG
from,O
1998,B-DATE
through,I-DATE
1999,I-DATE
",",O
President,B-TITLE
of,O
Furman,B-ORG
Selz,I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
from,O
1995,B-DATE
through,I-DATE
1997,I-DATE
and,O
as,O
a,O
Managing,B-TITLE
Director,I-TITLE
of,O
Lehman,B-ORG
Brothers,I-ORG
and,O
its,O
predecessors,O
from,O
1978,B-DATE
through,I-DATE
1994,I-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Shutzer,B-PERSON
serves,O
on,O
the,O
Board,B-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Directors,I-TITLE
of,O
ExamWorks,B-ORG
Group,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
and,O
Evercore,B-ORG
Trust,I-ORG
Company,I-ORG
.,O
,
He,O
has,O
also,O
served,O
on,O
the,O
Board,B-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Directors,I-TITLE
of,O
the,O
following,O
public,O
company,O
during,O
the,O
past,B-DATE
five,I-DATE
years,I-DATE
:,O
Mecklermedia,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
(,O
formerly,O
known,O
as,O
Mediabistro,B-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
),O
.,O
,
Key,O
Skills,O
:,O
finance,O
",",O
investor,O
relations,O
and,O
strategic,O
planning,O
.,O
,
Robert,B-PERSON
S.,I-PERSON
Singer,I-PERSON
-,O
Mr.,O
Singer,B-PERSON
",",O
67,B-DATE
",",O
became,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Tiffany,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
in,O
2012,B-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
has,O
been,O
a,O
consultant,O
for,O
IDG,B-ORG
Capital,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
private,O
equity,O
firm,O
",",O
since,O
November,B-DATE
1,I-DATE
",",I-DATE
2018,I-DATE
",",O
and,O
previously,O
served,O
as,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Barilla,B-ORG
Holding,I-ORG
S.p.A,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
major,O
Italian,B-NORP
food,O
company,O
",",O
from,O
2006,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2009,I-DATE
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
joining,O
Abercrombie,B-ORG
",",O
Mr.,O
Singer,B-PERSON
served,O
as,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Financial,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
Gucci,B-ORG
Group,I-ORG
NV,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
leading,O
luxury,O
goods,O
company,O
",",O
from,O
1995,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2004,I-DATE
.,O
,
From,O
1987,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
1995,I-DATE
",",O
Mr.,O
Singer,B-PERSON
was,O
a,O
Partner,B-TITLE
at,O
Coopers,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Lybrand,I-ORG
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Singer,B-PERSON
served,O
on,O
the,O
Board,B-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Directors,I-TITLE
of,O
Benetton,B-ORG
S.p.A.,I-ORG
from,O
2006,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2010,I-DATE
",",O
and,O
on,O
the,O
Board,B-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Directors,I-TITLE
of,O
Fairmont,B-ORG
Hotels,I-ORG
&,I-ORG
Resorts,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
from,O
2003,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2006,I-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Singer,B-PERSON
currently,O
serves,O
on,O
the,O
Board,B-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Directors,I-TITLE
of,O
Coty,B-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
and,O
Keurig,B-ORG
Dr.,I-ORG
Pepper,I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
",",O
and,O
served,O
on,O
the,O
Board,B-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Directors,I-TITLE
of,O
the,O
following,O
public,O
companies,O
during,O
the,O
past,B-DATE
five,I-DATE
years,I-DATE
:,O
Mead,B-ORG
Johnson,I-ORG
Nutrition,I-ORG
Company,I-ORG
and,O
Jimmy,B-ORG
Choo,I-ORG
PLC,I-ORG
.,O
,
Key,O
Skills,O
:,O
accounting,O
",",O
global,O
retail,O
",",O
financial,O
and,O
general,O
management,O
of,O
luxury,O
brands,O
.,O
,
Francesco,B-PERSON
Trapani,I-PERSON
-,O
Mr.,O
Trapani,B-PERSON
",",O
62,B-DATE
",",O
became,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Tiffany,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
in,O
March,B-DATE
2017,I-DATE
.,O
,
From,O
1984,B-DATE
until,I-DATE
2012,I-DATE
",",O
Mr.,O
Trapani,B-PERSON
served,O
as,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Bulgari,B-ORG
S.p.A.,I-ORG
(,O
``,O
Bulgari,B-ORG
'',O
),O
",",O
including,O
in,O
connection,O
with,O
the,O
company,O
's,O
listing,O
on,O
the,O
Italian,B-ORG
Stock,I-ORG
Exchange,I-ORG
",",O
creation,O
of,O
Bulgari,B-ORG
Hotels,I-ORG
&,I-ORG
Resorts,I-ORG
",",O
and,O
acquisition,O
by,O
LVMH,B-ORG
Moët,I-ORG
Hennessy,I-ORG
–,I-ORG
Louis,I-ORG
Vuitton,I-ORG
S.A.,I-ORG
(,O
``,O
LVMH,B-ORG
'',O
),O
in,O
2011,B-DATE
.,O
,
While,O
he,O
remained,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Bulgari,B-ORG
following,O
2012,B-DATE
",",O
he,O
resigned,O
such,O
role,O
in,O
February,B-DATE
2017,I-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Trapani,B-PERSON
was,O
named,O
as,O
a,O
defendant,O
",",O
in,O
his,O
capacity,O
as,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Bulgari,B-ORG
and,O
along,O
with,O
other,O
directors,O
and,O
managers,O
thereof,O
",",O
in,O
a,O
criminal,O
proceeding,O
in,O
Italy,B-GPE
related,O
to,O
an,O
alleged,O
violation,O
of,O
the,O
Italian,B-NORP
tax,O
laws,O
resulting,O
from,O
the,O
tax,O
treatment,O
of,O
certain,O
intercompany,O
dividend,O
payments,O
made,O
to,O
Bulgari,B-ORG
beginning,O
in,O
2008,B-DATE
.,O
,
The,O
tax,O
treatment,O
of,O
such,O
dividend,O
payments,O
was,O
determined,O
based,O
on,O
the,O
advice,O
of,O
Bulgari,B-ORG
's,O
tax,O
advisors,O
and,O
auditors,O
",",O
after,O
analysis,O
of,O
all,O
applicable,O
rules,O
",",O
regulations,O
and,O
related,O
interpretations,O
.,O
,
Further,O
",",O
the,O
tax,O
treatment,O
of,O
such,O
dividend,O
payments,O
was,O
previously,O
reviewed,O
",",O
in,O
a,O
separate,O
administrative,O
proceeding,O
",",O
by,O
the,O
Italian,B-ORG
Revenue,I-ORG
Agency,I-ORG
who,O
deemed,O
them,O
to,O
be,O
in,O
compliance,O
with,O
applicable,O
Italian,B-NORP
tax,O
laws,O
.,O
,
In,O
April,B-DATE
2018,I-DATE
",",O
the,O
Court,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Rome,I-ORG
dismissed,O
the,O
last,O
charge,O
pending,O
against,O
Mr.,O
Trapani,B-PERSON
.,O
,
The,O
public,O
prosecutor,O
has,O
appealed,O
the,O
Court,B-ORG
's,O
dismissal,O
and,O
that,O
appeal,O
is,O
currently,O
pending,O
.,O
,
From,O
2011,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2014,I-DATE
",",O
Mr.,O
Trapani,B-PERSON
also,O
served,O
as,O
Chairman,B-TITLE
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
LVMH,B-ORG
Watches,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
Jewelry,I-ORG
Division,I-ORG
and,O
on,O
the,O
Board,B-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Directors,I-TITLE
of,O
LVMH,B-ORG
;,O
following,O
2014,B-DATE
",",O
he,O
continued,O
to,O
serve,O
on,O
the,O
LVMH,B-ORG
Board,I-ORG
and,O
as,O
a,O
senior,B-TITLE
advisor,I-TITLE
to,O
the,O
LVMH,B-ORG
CEO,B-TITLE
until,O
2016,B-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Trapani,B-PERSON
joined,O
Clessidra,B-ORG
SGR,I-ORG
",",O
the,O
largest,O
private,O
equity,O
fund,O
in,O
Italy,B-GPE
",",O
as,O
Executive,B-TITLE
Vice-Chairman,I-TITLE
in,O
2014,B-DATE
",",O
and,O
later,O
served,O
as,O
Chairman,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Board,B-ORG
until,O
the,O
company,O
's,O
sale,O
in,O
2016,B-DATE
.,O
,
In,O
2016,B-DATE
",",O
Mr.,O
Trapani,B-PERSON
became,O
the,O
Executive,B-TITLE
Deputy,I-TITLE
Chairman,I-TITLE
and,O
a,O
partner,B-TITLE
of,O
Tages,B-ORG
Holding,I-ORG
S.p.A.,I-ORG
",",O
an,O
asset,O
management,O
firm,O
.,O
,
Key,O
Skills,O
:,O
luxury,O
brand,O
management,O
",",O
product,O
development,O
",",O
merchandising,O
",",O
finance,O
",",O
strategic,O
planning,O
and,O
global,O
management,O
.,O
,
Annie,B-PERSON
Young-Scrivner,I-PERSON
-,O
Ms.,O
Young-Scrivner,B-PERSON
",",O
50,B-DATE
",",O
became,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Tiffany,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
in,O
May,B-DATE
2018,I-DATE
.,O
,
She,O
is,O
the,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Godiva,B-ORG
Chocolatier,I-ORG
(,O
``,O
Godiva,B-ORG
'',O
),O
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
joining,O
Godiva,B-ORG
in,O
August,B-DATE
2017,I-DATE
",",O
Ms.,O
Young-Scrivner,B-PERSON
held,O
senior,O
positions,O
at,O
Starbucks,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
(,O
``,O
Starbucks,B-ORG
'',O
),O
beginning,O
in,O
2009,B-DATE
",",O
including,O
as,O
Global,B-TITLE
Chief,I-TITLE
Marketing,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
&,O
President,B-TITLE
of,O
Tazo,B-ORG
Tea,I-ORG
from,O
2009,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2012,I-DATE
",",O
President,B-TITLE
of,O
Starbucks,B-ORG
Canada,I-ORG
from,O
2012,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2014,I-DATE
",",O
President,B-TITLE
",",O
Teavana,B-ORG
&,O
Executive,B-TITLE
Vice,I-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
of,O
Global,B-ORG
Tea,I-ORG
from,O
2014,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2015,I-DATE
",",O
and,O
Executive,B-TITLE
Vice,I-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
",",O
Global,B-ORG
Digital,I-ORG
&,I-ORG
Loyalty,I-ORG
Development,I-ORG
from,O
2015,B-DATE
until,O
her,O
departure,O
in,O
April,B-DATE
2017,I-DATE
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
joining,O
Starbucks,B-ORG
",",O
Ms.,O
Young-Scrivner,B-PERSON
held,O
senior,O
leadership,O
positions,O
at,O
PepsiCo,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
in,O
sales,O
",",O
marketing,O
and,O
general,O
management,O
",",O
including,O
her,O
role,O
as,O
Region,B-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
of,O
PepsiCo,B-ORG
Foods,I-ORG
Greater,I-ORG
China,I-ORG
from,O
2006,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2008,I-DATE
.,O
,
Ms.,O
Young-Scrivner,B-PERSON
holds,O
a,O
B.A,B-PRODUCT
.,O
from,O
the,O
Foster,B-ORG
School,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Business,I-ORG
",",O
University,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Washington,I-ORG
and,O
an,O
Executive,B-PRODUCT
M.B.A.,I-PRODUCT
from,O
the,O
Carlson,B-ORG
School,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Business,I-ORG
",",O
University,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Minnesota,I-ORG
.,O
,
Ms.,O
Young-Scrivner,B-PERSON
also,O
served,O
on,O
the,O
Board,B-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Directors,I-TITLE
of,O
the,O
following,O
public,O
company,O
during,O
the,O
past,B-DATE
five,I-DATE
years,I-DATE
:,O
Macy,B-ORG
's,I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
Key,O
Skills,O
:,O
omnichannel,O
brand,O
management,O
",",O
digital,O
marketing,O
",",O
global,O
management,O
",",O
consumer,O
insights,O
and,O
data,O
analytics,O
",",O
and,O
strategic,O
planning,O
.,O
,
SAMUEL,B-PERSON
R.,I-PERSON
ALLEN,I-PERSON
-,O
Mr.,O
Allen,B-PERSON
",",O
65,B-DATE
",",O
has,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
since,O
2010,B-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Allen,B-PERSON
has,O
been,O
Chairman,B-TITLE
and,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Executive,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
Deere,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
farm,O
machinery,O
and,O
equipment,O
company,O
",",O
since,O
2010,B-DATE
",",O
and,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
since,O
2009,B-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Allen,B-PERSON
joined,O
Deere,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
in,O
1975,B-DATE
and,O
since,O
that,O
time,O
has,O
held,O
positions,O
of,O
increasing,O
responsibility,O
.,O
,
Committees,O
:,O
Corporate,B-ORG
Governance,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
Nominating,I-ORG
(,O
chair,B-TITLE
),O
;,O
Human,B-ORG
Resources,I-ORG
.,O
,
GREG,B-PERSON
CREED,I-PERSON
-,O
Mr.,O
Creed,B-PERSON
",",O
61,B-DATE
",",O
has,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
since,O
2017,B-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Creed,B-PERSON
has,O
been,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Executive,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
Yum,B-ORG
!,I-ORG
Brands,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
leading,O
operator,O
of,O
quick,O
service,O
restaurants,O
",",O
since,O
2015,B-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
served,O
as,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Executive,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
Taco,B-ORG
Bell,I-ORG
Division,I-ORG
from,O
2011,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2014,I-DATE
",",O
and,O
as,O
President,B-TITLE
and,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Concept,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
Taco,B-ORG
Bell,I-ORG
U.S.,I-ORG
from,O
2007,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2011,I-DATE
after,O
holding,O
other,O
positions,O
of,O
increasing,O
responsibility,O
with,O
the,O
company,O
since,O
1994,B-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Creed,B-PERSON
has,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Yum,B-ORG
!,I-ORG
since,O
2014,B-DATE
and,O
previously,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
International,B-ORG
Game,I-ORG
Technology,I-ORG
from,O
2010,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2015,I-DATE
.,O
,
Committees,O
:,O
Human,B-ORG
Resources,I-ORG
;,O
Finance,B-ORG
.,O
,
DIANE,B-PERSON
M.,I-PERSON
DIETZ,I-PERSON
-,O
Ms.,O
Dietz,B-PERSON
",",O
53,B-DATE
",",O
has,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
since,O
2013,B-DATE
.,O
,
Ms.,O
Dietz,B-PERSON
has,O
been,O
the,O
President,B-TITLE
and,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Executive,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
Rodan,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Fields,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
LLC,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
leading,O
premium,O
skincare,O
company,O
",",O
since,O
2016,B-DATE
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
joining,O
Safeway,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
",",O
Ms.,O
Dietz,B-PERSON
held,O
positions,O
of,O
increasing,O
responsibility,O
with,O
Procter,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Gamble,I-ORG
from,O
1989,B-DATE
through,I-DATE
2008,I-DATE
.,O
,
Committees,O
:,O
Corporate,B-ORG
Governance,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
Nominating,I-ORG
;,O
Human,B-ORG
Resources,I-ORG
.,O
,
GERRI,B-PERSON
T.,I-PERSON
ELLIOTT,I-PERSON
-,O
Ms.,O
Elliott,B-PERSON
",",O
62,B-DATE
",",O
has,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
since,O
2014,B-DATE
.,O
,
Ms.,O
Elliott,B-PERSON
has,O
served,O
as,O
the,O
Executive,B-TITLE
Vice,I-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
and,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Sales,I-TITLE
and,I-TITLE
Marketing,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
Cisco,B-ORG
Systems,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
since,O
April,B-DATE
2018,I-DATE
.,O
,
Ms.,O
Elliott,B-PERSON
previously,O
served,O
as,O
the,O
Executive,B-TITLE
Vice,I-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
",",O
Strategic,B-TITLE
Advisor,I-TITLE
and,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Customer,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
Juniper,B-ORG
Networks,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
producer,O
of,O
high-performance,O
networking,O
equipment,O
",",O
from,O
2013,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2014,I-DATE
.,O
,
Ms.,O
Elliott,B-PERSON
began,O
her,O
employment,O
with,O
Juniper,B-ORG
Networks,I-ORG
in,O
2009,B-DATE
and,O
held,O
positions,O
of,O
increasing,O
responsibility,O
with,O
the,O
company,O
through,O
2014,B-DATE
.,O
,
Before,O
joining,O
Juniper,B-ORG
Networks,I-ORG
",",O
Ms.,O
Elliott,B-PERSON
was,O
at,O
Microsoft,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
",",O
where,O
she,O
was,O
Corporate,B-TITLE
Vice,I-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
",",O
Worldwide,B-ORG
Public,I-ORG
Sector,I-ORG
Organization,I-ORG
from,O
2004,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2008,I-DATE
.,O
,
Ms.,O
Elliott,B-PERSON
was,O
previously,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Bed,B-ORG
Bath,I-ORG
&,I-ORG
Beyond,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
(,O
2014,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2017,I-DATE
),O
",",O
Imperva,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
(,O
2015,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2018,I-DATE
),O
",",O
Marvell,B-ORG
Technology,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
Ltd.,I-ORG
(,O
2017,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2018,I-DATE
),O
",",O
and,O
Mimecast,B-ORG
Limited,I-ORG
(,O
2017,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2018,I-DATE
),O
.,O
,
Committees,O
:,O
Audit,B-ORG
;,O
Finance,B-ORG
.,O
,
MICHAEL,B-PERSON
F.,I-PERSON
JOHNSTON,I-PERSON
-,O
Mr.,O
Johnston,B-PERSON
",",O
71,B-DATE
",",O
has,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
since,O
2003,B-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Johnston,B-PERSON
retired,O
from,O
Visteon,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
",",O
an,O
automotive,O
components,O
supplier,O
",",O
in,O
2008,B-DATE
.,O
,
At,O
Visteon,B-ORG
",",O
he,O
served,O
as,O
Chairman,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Board,B-ORG
and,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Executive,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
",",O
President,B-TITLE
",",O
and,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Operating,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
at,O
various,O
times,O
since,B-DATE
2000,I-DATE
.,O
,
In,O
May,B-DATE
2009,I-DATE
",",O
Visteon,B-ORG
filed,O
for,O
voluntary,O
reorganization,O
under,O
Chapter,B-LAW
11,I-LAW
of,O
the,O
U.S.,B-LAW
Bankruptcy,I-LAW
Code,I-LAW
.,O
,
Before,O
joining,O
Visteon,B-ORG
",",O
Mr.,O
Johnston,B-PERSON
held,O
various,O
positions,O
in,O
the,O
automotive,O
and,O
building,O
services,O
industry,O
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Johnston,B-PERSON
is,O
also,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Armstrong,B-ORG
Flooring,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
(,O
since,O
2016,B-DATE
),O
and,O
Dover,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
(,O
since,O
2013,B-DATE
),O
",",O
and,O
previously,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Armstrong,B-ORG
World,I-ORG
Industries,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
(,O
2010,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2016,I-DATE
),O
",",O
and,O
Flowserve,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
(,O
1997,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2013,I-DATE
),O
.,O
,
Committees,O
:,O
Audit,B-ORG
;,O
Human,B-ORG
Resources,I-ORG
(,O
chair,B-TITLE
),O
.,O
,
JOHN,B-PERSON
D.,I-PERSON
LIU,I-PERSON
-,O
Mr.,O
Liu,B-PERSON
",",O
50,B-DATE
",",O
has,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
since,O
2010,B-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Liu,B-PERSON
has,O
been,O
the,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Executive,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
Essex,B-ORG
Equity,I-ORG
Management,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
financial,O
services,O
company,O
",",O
and,O
Managing,B-TITLE
Partner,I-TITLE
of,O
Richmond,B-ORG
Hill,I-ORG
Investments,I-ORG
",",O
an,O
investment,O
management,O
firm,O
",",O
since,O
2008,B-DATE
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
that,O
time,O
",",O
Mr.,O
Liu,B-PERSON
was,O
employed,O
for,O
12,B-DATE
years,I-DATE
by,O
Greenhill,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
global,O
investment,O
banking,O
firm,O
",",O
in,O
positions,O
of,O
increasing,O
responsibility,O
including,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Financial,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Liu,B-PERSON
has,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Greenhill,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
since,O
2017,B-DATE
.,O
,
Committees,O
:,O
Audit,B-ORG
;,O
Finance,B-ORG
.,O
,
JAMES,B-PERSON
M.,I-PERSON
LOREE,I-PERSON
-,O
Mr.,O
Loree,B-PERSON
",",O
60,B-DATE
",",O
has,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
since,O
2017,B-DATE
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
joining,O
Stanley,B-ORG
Black,I-ORG
&,I-ORG
Decker,I-ORG
",",O
Mr.,O
Loree,B-PERSON
held,O
positions,O
of,O
increasing,O
responsibility,O
in,O
financial,O
and,O
operating,O
management,O
in,O
business,O
",",O
corporate,O
and,O
financial,O
services,O
at,O
General,B-ORG
Electric,I-ORG
from,O
1980,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
1999,I-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Loree,B-PERSON
has,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Stanley,B-ORG
Black,I-ORG
&,I-ORG
Decker,I-ORG
since,B-DATE
2016,I-DATE
",",O
and,O
previously,O
served,O
on,O
the,O
board,B-ORG
of,O
Harsco,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
from,O
2010,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2016,I-DATE
and,O
as,O
chairman,B-TITLE
of,O
Harsco,B-ORG
's,O
Audit,B-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
from,O
2012,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2016,I-DATE
.,O
,
Committees,O
:,O
Audit,B-ORG
;,O
Corporate,B-ORG
Governance,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
Nominating,I-ORG
.,O
,
HARISH,B-PERSON
MANWANI,I-PERSON
-,O
Mr.,O
Manwani,B-PERSON
",",O
65,B-DATE
",",O
has,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
since,O
2011,B-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Manwani,B-PERSON
is,O
a,O
Senior,B-TITLE
Operating,I-TITLE
Partner,I-TITLE
for,O
Blackstone,B-ORG
Group,I-ORG
",",O
having,O
served,O
with,O
Blackstone,B-ORG
since,O
2015,B-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Manwani,B-PERSON
is,O
the,O
former,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Operating,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
Unilever,B-ORG
",",O
a,O
global,O
consumer,O
product,O
brands,O
company,O
",",O
a,O
position,O
he,O
was,O
appointed,O
to,O
in,O
2011,B-DATE
and,O
held,O
until,O
his,O
retirement,O
in,O
2014,B-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Manwani,B-PERSON
is,O
also,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Gilead,B-ORG
Sciences,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
(,O
since,O
May,B-DATE
2018,I-DATE
),O
",",O
Qualcomm,B-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
(,O
since,O
2014,B-DATE
),O
and,O
Nielsen,B-ORG
Holdings,I-ORG
plc,I-ORG
(,O
since,O
2015,B-DATE
),O
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Manwani,B-PERSON
previously,O
served,O
as,O
the,O
non-executive,B-TITLE
Chairman,I-TITLE
of,O
Hindustan,B-ORG
Unilever,I-ORG
Limited,I-ORG
(,O
2005,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2018,I-DATE
),O
and,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Pearson,B-ORG
plc,I-ORG
(,O
2013,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2018,I-DATE
),O
.,O
,
Committees,O
:,O
Corporate,B-ORG
Governance,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
Nominating,I-ORG
;,O
Human,B-ORG
Resources,I-ORG
.,O
,
LARRY,B-PERSON
O.,I-PERSON
SPENCER,I-PERSON
-,O
Spencer,B-PERSON
",",O
65,B-DATE
",",O
has,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
since,O
2016,B-DATE
.,O
,
General,B-TITLE
Spencer,B-PERSON
served,O
until,O
March,B-DATE
1,I-DATE
",",I-DATE
2019,I-DATE
as,O
President,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Air,B-ORG
Force,I-ORG
Association,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
position,O
he,O
held,O
since,O
his,O
retirement,O
as,O
a,O
four-star,B-TITLE
general,I-TITLE
in,O
2015,B-DATE
after,O
serving,O
44,B-DATE
years,I-DATE
with,O
the,O
United,B-ORG
States,I-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Force,I-ORG
.,O
,
General,B-TITLE
Spencer,B-PERSON
held,O
positions,O
of,O
increasing,O
responsibility,O
with,O
the,O
Air,B-ORG
Force,I-ORG
",",O
which,O
included,O
Vice,B-TITLE
Chief,I-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Staff,I-TITLE
",",O
the,O
second,B-ORDINAL
highest-ranking,O
military,O
member,O
in,O
the,O
Air,B-ORG
Force,I-ORG
.,O
,
General,B-TITLE
Spencer,B-PERSON
was,O
the,O
first,B-ORDINAL
Air,B-TITLE
Force,I-TITLE
officer,I-TITLE
to,O
serve,O
as,O
the,O
Assistant,B-TITLE
Chief,I-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
Staff,I-TITLE
in,O
the,O
White,B-ORG
House,I-ORG
Military,I-ORG
Office,I-ORG
and,O
he,O
served,O
as,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Financial,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
and,O
then,O
Director,B-TITLE
of,O
Mission,B-ORG
Support,I-ORG
at,O
a,O
major,O
command,O
.,O
,
General,B-TITLE
Spencer,B-PERSON
is,O
also,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Triumph,B-ORG
Group,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
(,O
since,O
2018,B-DATE
),O
.,O
,
Committees,O
:,O
Corporate,B-ORG
Governance,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
Nominating,I-ORG
;,O
Finance,B-ORG
.,O
,
MICHAEL,B-PERSON
D.,I-PERSON
WHITE,I-PERSON
-,O
Mr.,O
White,B-PERSON
",",O
67,B-DATE
",",O
has,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
since,O
2004,B-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
White,B-PERSON
served,O
as,O
an,O
Advisory,B-TITLE
Partner,I-TITLE
for,O
Trian,B-ORG
Fund,I-ORG
Management,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
L.P.,I-ORG
from,O
2016,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2017,I-DATE
",",O
and,O
was,O
the,O
Chairman,B-TITLE
",",O
President,B-TITLE
and,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Executive,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
DIRECTV,B-ORG
",",O
a,O
leading,O
provider,O
of,O
digital,O
television,O
entertainment,O
services,O
",",O
from,O
2010,B-DATE
until,O
his,O
retirement,O
in,O
2015,B-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
also,O
served,O
as,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
company,O
from,O
2009,B-DATE
until,I-DATE
2015,I-DATE
.,O
,
From,O
2003,B-DATE
until,I-DATE
2009,I-DATE
",",O
Mr.,O
White,B-PERSON
was,O
Chief,B-TITLE
Executive,I-TITLE
Officer,I-TITLE
of,O
PepsiCo,B-ORG
International,I-ORG
",",O
and,O
Vice,B-TITLE
Chairman,I-TITLE
",",O
PepsiCo,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
after,O
holding,O
positions,O
of,O
increasing,O
responsibility,O
with,O
PepsiCo,B-ORG
since,O
1990,B-DATE
.,O
,
Mr.,O
White,B-PERSON
is,O
also,O
a,O
director,B-TITLE
of,O
Kimberly-Clark,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
(,O
since,O
2015,B-DATE
),O
and,O
Bank,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
America,I-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
(,O
since,O
2016,B-DATE
),O
.,O
,
Committees,O
:,O
Audit,B-ORG
(,O
chair,B-TITLE
),O
;,O
Corporate,B-ORG
Governance,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
Nominating,I-ORG
.,O
,
Patricia,B-PERSON
M.,I-PERSON
Bedient,I-PERSON
",",O
65,B-DATE
.,O
,
Former,B-TITLE
Executive,I-TITLE
Vice,I-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
and,O
CFO,B-TITLE
",",O
The,B-ORG
Weyerhaeuser,I-ORG
Company,I-ORG
.,O
,
Director,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
since,O
2004,B-DATE
.,O
,
Lead,B-TITLE
Independent,I-TITLE
Director,I-TITLE
.,O
,
Audit,B-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
.,O
,
Governance,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
Nominating,I-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
.,O
,
Qualifications,O
:,O
Financial,O
Expertise,O
.,O
,
Strategic,O
Planning,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Public,O
Accounting,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Mergers,O
and,O
Acquisitions,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Professional,O
Highlights,O
:,O
Ms.,O
Bedient,B-PERSON
was,O
executive,B-TITLE
vice,I-TITLE
president,I-TITLE
(,O
until,O
July,B-DATE
2016,I-DATE
),O
for,O
The,B-ORG
Weyerhaeuser,I-ORG
Company,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
publicly,O
traded,O
company,O
and,O
one,O
of,O
the,O
world,O
',O
s,O
largest,O
integrated,O
forest,O
products,O
companies,O
.,O
,
She,O
was,O
the,O
company,O
',O
s,O
CFO,B-TITLE
until,O
February,B-DATE
2016,I-DATE
.,O
,
A,O
certified,B-TITLE
public,I-TITLE
accountant,I-TITLE
(,O
CPA,B-TITLE
),O
since,O
1978,B-DATE
",",O
she,O
served,O
as,O
managing,B-TITLE
partner,I-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Seattle,B-GPE
office,O
of,O
Arthur,B-ORG
Andersen,I-ORG
LLP,I-ORG
prior,O
to,O
joining,O
Weyerhaeuser,B-ORG
.,O
,
Ms.,O
Bedient,B-PERSON
also,O
worked,O
at,O
Andersen,B-ORG
',O
s,O
Portland,B-GPE
and,O
Boise,B-GPE
offices,O
as,O
a,O
partner,B-TITLE
and,O
as,O
a,O
CPA,B-TITLE
during,O
her,O
27-year,B-DATE
career,O
with,O
the,O
firm,O
.,O
,
She,O
is,O
a,O
member,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
American,B-ORG
Institute,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
CPAs,I-ORG
and,O
the,O
Washington,B-ORG
Society,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
CPAs,I-ORG
.,O
,
Current,O
Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Suncor,B-ORG
Energy,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
Park,B-ORG
Hotels,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
Resorts,I-ORG
.,O
,
Current,O
Non-Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
and,O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
(,O
subsidiaries,O
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
),O
.,O
,
Overlake,B-ORG
Hospital,I-ORG
Medical,I-ORG
Center,I-ORG
Board,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Trustees,I-ORG
.,O
,
Oregon,B-ORG
State,I-ORG
University,I-ORG
Board,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Trustees,I-ORG
.,O
,
University,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Washington,I-ORG
Foster,I-ORG
School,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Business,I-ORG
Advisory,I-ORG
Board,I-ORG
.,O
,
Education,O
:,O
BS,B-PRODUCT
",",O
Oregon,B-ORG
State,I-ORG
University,I-ORG
.,O
,
James,B-PERSON
A,I-PERSON
.,I-PERSON
Beer,I-PERSON
",",O
58,B-DATE
.,O
,
CFO,B-TITLE
",",O
Atlassian,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
.,O
,
Director,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
since,O
2017,B-DATE
.,O
,
Compensation,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
Leadership,I-ORG
Development,I-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
.,O
,
Safety,B-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
.,O
,
Qualifications,O
:,O
Financial,O
Expertise,O
.,O
,
Aviation,O
Industry,O
Expertise,O
.,O
,
Strategic,O
Planning,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Technology,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Professional,O
Highlights,O
:,O
Mr.,O
Beer,B-PERSON
joined,O
Atlassian,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
PLC,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
publicly,O
traded,O
company,O
",",O
as,O
its,O
CFO,B-TITLE
in,O
February,B-DATE
2018,I-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
was,O
executive,B-TITLE
vice,I-TITLE
president,I-TITLE
and,O
CFO,B-TITLE
for,O
McKesson,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
from,O
2013,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2017,I-DATE
",",O
and,O
CFO,B-TITLE
at,O
Symantec,B-ORG
Corp.,I-ORG
from,O
2006,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2013,I-DATE
.,O
,
From,O
1991,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2006,I-DATE
",",O
he,O
held,O
a,O
number,O
of,O
management,O
positions,O
including,O
CFO,B-TITLE
at,O
AMR,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
and,O
American,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
",",O
AMR,B-ORG
',O
s,O
principal,O
subsidiary,O
.,O
,
Current,O
Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
ForeScout,B-ORG
Technologies,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
Current,O
Non-Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
and,O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
(,O
subsidiaries,O
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
),O
.,O
,
Education,O
:,O
BS,B-PRODUCT
Aeronautical,I-PRODUCT
Engineering,I-PRODUCT
",",O
Imperial,B-ORG
College,I-ORG
",",O
London,B-ORG
University,I-ORG
.,O
,
MBA,B-PRODUCT
",",O
Harvard,B-ORG
Business,I-ORG
School,I-ORG
.,O
,
Marion,B-PERSON
C.,I-PERSON
Blakey,I-PERSON
",",O
71,B-DATE
-,O
Former,B-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
",",O
Rolls-Royce,B-ORG
North,I-ORG
America,I-ORG
.,O
,
Director,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
since,O
2010,B-DATE
.,O
,
Compensation,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
Leadership,I-ORG
Development,I-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
(,O
Chair,B-TITLE
),O
.,O
,
Safety,B-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
.,O
,
Qualifications,O
:,O
Extensive,O
experience,O
with,O
airline,O
industry,O
government,O
and,O
trade,O
organizations,O
including,O
:,O
Aviation,O
Industry,O
Expertise,O
.,O
,
Professional,O
Highlights,O
:,O
Ms.,O
Blakey,B-PERSON
was,O
president,B-TITLE
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Rolls-Royce,B-ORG
North,I-ORG
America,I-ORG
until,O
June,B-DATE
30,I-DATE
",",I-DATE
2018,I-DATE
.,O
,
From,O
2007,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2015,I-DATE
",",O
she,O
was,O
president,B-TITLE
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Aerospace,B-ORG
Industries,I-ORG
Association,I-ORG
",",O
the,O
nation,O
',O
s,O
largest,O
aerospace,O
and,O
defense,O
trade,O
association,O
.,O
,
She,O
previously,O
served,O
on,O
the,O
President,B-ORG
',I-ORG
s,I-ORG
Export,I-ORG
Council,I-ORG
Subcommittee,I-ORG
on,I-ORG
Export,I-ORG
Administration,I-ORG
",",O
the,O
Washington,B-ORG
Area,I-ORG
Airports,I-ORG
Task,I-ORG
Force,I-ORG
Advisory,I-ORG
Board,I-ORG
and,O
the,O
International,B-ORG
Aviation,I-ORG
Women,I-ORG
',I-ORG
s,I-ORG
Association,I-ORG
Advisory,I-ORG
Board,I-ORG
.,O
,
Current,O
Non-Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
and,O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
(,O
subsidiaries,O
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
),O
.,O
,
Noblis,B-ORG
Board,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Trustees,I-ORG
(,O
a,O
non-profit,O
science,O
",",O
technology,O
and,O
strategy,O
organization,O
),O
.,O
,
Cobham,B-ORG
Plc,I-ORG
.,O
,
Aireon,B-ORG
Advisory,I-ORG
Board,I-ORG
.,O
,
Sunrise,B-ORG
Transportation,I-ORG
Advisory,I-ORG
Board,I-ORG
.,O
,
Education,O
:,O
BA,B-PRODUCT
",",O
Mary,B-ORG
Washington,I-ORG
College,I-ORG
of,O
the,O
University,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Virginia,I-ORG
.,O
,
Phyllis,B-PERSON
J.,I-PERSON
Campbell,I-PERSON
",",O
67,B-DATE
.,O
,
Chairman,B-TITLE
",",O
JPMorgan,B-ORG
Chase,I-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
Pacific,B-GPE
Northwest,I-GPE
Region,I-GPE
.,O
,
Director,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
since,O
2002,B-DATE
.,O
,
Governance,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
Nominating,I-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
(,O
Chair,B-TITLE
),O
.,O
,
Qualifications,O
:,O
Extensive,O
Business,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Community,O
Leadership,O
.,O
,
Governance,O
Expertise,O
.,O
,
Professional,O
Highlights,O
:,O
Since,O
April,B-DATE
2009,I-DATE
",",O
Ms.,O
Campbell,B-PERSON
has,O
been,O
chairman,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Pacific,B-GPE
Northwest,I-GPE
Region,I-GPE
for,O
JPMorgan,B-ORG
Chase,I-ORG
&,I-ORG
Co.,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
publicly,O
traded,O
company,O
.,O
,
She,O
is,O
the,O
firm,O
',O
s,O
senior,B-TITLE
executive,I-TITLE
in,O
Washington,B-GPE
",",O
Oregon,B-GPE
and,O
Idaho,B-LOC
",",O
representing,O
JPMorgan,B-ORG
Chase,I-ORG
at,O
the,O
most,O
senior,O
level,O
.,O
,
From,O
2003,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2009,I-DATE
",",O
Ms.,O
Campbell,B-PERSON
served,O
as,O
president,B-TITLE
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
The,B-ORG
Seattle,I-ORG
Foundation,I-ORG
",",O
one,O
of,O
the,O
nation,O
',O
s,O
largest,O
community,O
philanthropic,O
foundations,O
.,O
,
She,O
was,O
president,B-TITLE
of,O
U.S.,B-ORG
Bank,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Washington,I-ORG
from,O
1993,B-DATE
until,I-DATE
2001,I-DATE
and,O
served,O
as,O
chair,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
bank,B-ORG
',I-ORG
s,I-ORG
Community,I-ORG
Board,I-ORG
.,O
,
Ms.,O
Campbell,B-PERSON
has,O
received,O
several,O
awards,O
for,O
her,O
corporate,O
and,O
community,O
involvement,O
",",O
including,O
Women,B-PRODUCT
Who,I-PRODUCT
Make,I-PRODUCT
A,I-PRODUCT
Difference,I-PRODUCT
and,O
Director,B-PRODUCT
of,I-PRODUCT
the,I-PRODUCT
Year,I-PRODUCT
from,O
the,O
Northwest,B-ORG
Chapter,I-ORG
of,O
the,O
National,B-ORG
Association,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Corporate,I-ORG
Directors,I-ORG
.,O
,
Current,O
Non-Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
and,O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
(,O
subsidiaries,O
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
),O
.,O
,
Toyota,B-ORG
',O
s,O
Diversity,B-ORG
Advisory,I-ORG
Board,I-ORG
.,O
,
Education,O
:,O
BA,B-PRODUCT
",",O
Washington,B-ORG
State,I-ORG
University,I-ORG
.,O
,
MBA,B-PRODUCT
",",O
University,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Washington,I-ORG
.,O
,
Raymond,B-PERSON
L.,I-PERSON
Conner,I-PERSON
",",O
63,B-DATE
.,O
,
Former,B-TITLE
Vice,I-TITLE
Chairman,I-TITLE
",",O
The,B-ORG
Boeing,I-ORG
Company,I-ORG
.,O
,
Director,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
since,O
2018,B-DATE
.,O
,
Compensation,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
Leadership,I-ORG
Development,I-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
.,O
,
Safety,B-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
.,O
,
Qualifications,O
:,O
Public,O
Company,O
CEO,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Strategic,O
Planning,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Aviation,O
Industry,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Community,O
Leadership,O
.,O
,
Professional,O
Highlights,O
:,O
Mr.,O
Conner,B-PERSON
is,O
former,B-TITLE
vice,I-TITLE
chairman,I-TITLE
of,O
The,B-ORG
Boeing,I-ORG
Company,I-ORG
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
his,O
appointment,O
to,O
vice,B-TITLE
chairman,I-TITLE
in,O
2013,B-DATE
",",O
Mr.,O
Conner,B-PERSON
served,O
in,O
a,O
number,O
of,O
positions,O
with,O
Boeing,B-ORG
Commercial,I-ORG
Airplanes,I-ORG
since,O
1977,B-DATE
",",O
including,O
a,O
variety,O
of,O
roles,O
within,O
the,O
sales,O
",",O
finance,O
and,O
materiel,O
divisions,O
.,O
,
Most,O
recently,O
",",O
he,O
served,O
as,O
vice,B-TITLE
president,I-TITLE
and,O
general,B-TITLE
manager,I-TITLE
of,O
the,O
777,B-PRODUCT
program,O
(,O
2001-2003,B-DATE
),O
",",O
vice,B-TITLE
president,I-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
sales,I-TITLE
for,O
the,O
Americas,B-GPE
(,O
2003,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2007,I-DATE
),O
",",O
vice,B-TITLE
president,I-TITLE
and,O
general,B-TITLE
manager,I-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
supply,I-TITLE
chain,I-TITLE
management,I-TITLE
and,I-TITLE
operations,I-TITLE
(,O
2008,B-DATE
–,I-DATE
2011,I-DATE
),O
",",O
vice,B-TITLE
president,I-TITLE
sales,I-TITLE
",",I-TITLE
marketing,I-TITLE
and,I-TITLE
commercial,I-TITLE
aviation,I-TITLE
services,I-TITLE
(,O
2012,B-DATE
),O
",",O
and,O
president,B-TITLE
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
(,O
2013-2017,B-DATE
),O
.,O
,
Current,O
Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Adient,B-ORG
.,O
,
Current,O
Non-Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
and,O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
(,O
subsidiaries,O
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
),O
.,O
,
Boys,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
Girls,I-ORG
Clubs,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Bellevue,I-ORG
.,O
,
Board,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Trustees,I-ORG
Central,I-ORG
Washington,I-ORG
University,I-ORG
.,O
,
Education,O
:,O
BS,B-PRODUCT
",",O
Central,B-ORG
Washington,I-ORG
University,I-ORG
.,O
,
MBA,B-PRODUCT
",",O
University,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Puget,I-ORG
Sound,I-ORG
.,O
,
Dhiren,B-PERSON
R.,I-PERSON
Fonseca,I-PERSON
",",O
54,B-DATE
-,O
Partner,B-TITLE
",",O
Certares,B-ORG
LP,I-ORG
.,O
,
Director,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
since,O
2014,B-DATE
.,O
Audit,B-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
.,O
,
Qualifications,O
:,O
Technology/IT/Digital,O
Expertise,O
.,O
,
Business,O
Development,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Financial,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Professional,O
Highlights,O
:,O
Prior,O
to,O
joining,O
Certares,B-ORG
LP,I-ORG
as,O
a,O
partner,B-TITLE
in,O
December,B-DATE
2014,I-DATE
",",O
Mr.,O
Fonseca,B-PERSON
was,O
chief,B-TITLE
commercial,I-TITLE
officer,I-TITLE
at,O
Expedia,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
",",O
where,O
he,O
served,O
for,O
more,B-DATE
than,I-DATE
18,I-DATE
years,I-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
contributed,O
greatly,O
to,O
the,O
online,O
travel,O
company,O
',O
s,O
growth,O
and,O
success,O
",",O
serving,O
in,O
a,O
host,O
of,O
key,O
roles,O
including,O
co-president,B-TITLE
of,O
its,O
global,O
partner,O
services,O
group,O
and,O
senior,B-TITLE
vice,I-TITLE
president,I-TITLE
of,O
corporate,O
development,O
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Fonseca,B-PERSON
helped,O
found,O
Expedia.com,B-ORG
as,O
part,O
of,O
the,O
management,O
team,O
at,O
Microsoft,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
that,O
brought,O
the,O
online,O
travel,O
company,O
to,O
life,O
in,O
1995,B-DATE
and,O
subsequently,O
took,O
it,O
public,O
in,O
1999,B-DATE
.,O
,
Before,O
Expedia,B-ORG
",",O
he,O
held,O
multiple,O
roles,O
in,O
product,O
management,O
and,O
corporate,O
technical,O
sales,O
at,O
Microsoft,B-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
.,O
,
Current,O
Non-Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
and,O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
(,O
subsidiaries,O
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
),O
.,O
,
RentPath,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
Rackspace,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
Caesars,B-ORG
Resort,I-ORG
Collection,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
LLC,I-ORG
.,O
,
Susan,B-PERSON
J.,I-PERSON
Li,I-PERSON
",",O
33,B-DATE
-,O
Vice,B-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
Finance,I-TITLE
",",O
Facebook,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
Director,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
since,O
2018,B-DATE
.,O
,
Audit,B-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
.,O
,
Qualifications,O
:,O
Financial,O
Expertise,O
.,O
,
Strategic,O
Planning,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Technology/IT/Digital,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Professional,O
Highlights,O
:,O
Ms.,O
Li,B-PERSON
currently,O
serves,O
as,O
a,O
vice,B-TITLE
president,I-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
finance,I-TITLE
at,O
Facebook,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
",",O
where,O
she,O
leads,O
the,O
finance,O
and,O
business,O
planning,O
organization,O
.,O
,
Since,O
joining,O
Facebook,B-ORG
in,O
2008,B-DATE
",",O
Ms.,O
Li,B-PERSON
has,O
served,O
in,O
a,O
number,O
of,O
finance,O
positions,O
",",O
including,O
director,B-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
finance,I-TITLE
from,O
2013,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2016,I-DATE
",",O
leading,O
teams,O
focused,O
on,O
business,O
operations,O
and,O
financial,O
planning,O
and,O
analysis,O
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
Facebook,B-ORG
",",O
she,O
was,O
an,O
investment,O
banking,O
analyst,O
at,O
Morgan,B-ORG
Stanley,I-ORG
.,O
,
Current,O
Non-Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
and,O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
(,O
subsidiaries,O
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
),O
.,O
,
Education,O
:,O
BA,B-PRODUCT
and,O
BS,B-PRODUCT
",",O
Stanford,B-ORG
University,I-ORG
.,O
,
Helvi,B-PERSON
K.,I-PERSON
Sandvik,I-PERSON
",",O
61,B-DATE
-,O
President,B-TITLE
",",O
Kidways,B-ORG
LLC,I-ORG
.,I-ORG
and,O
Former,B-TITLE
President,I-TITLE
",",O
NANA,B-ORG
Development,I-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
.,O
,
Director,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
since,O
2013,B-DATE
.,O
,
Safety,B-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
(,O
Chair,B-TITLE
),O
.,O
,
Qualifications,O
:,O
30+,B-DATE
Years,I-DATE
of,O
Private,O
and,O
Public,O
Sector,O
Senior,O
Executive,O
Management,O
and,O
Board,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Intimate,O
Knowledge,O
of,O
the,O
Native,B-NORP
Culture,I-NORP
and,O
Transportation,O
Requirements,O
in,O
the,O
State,B-GPE
of,I-GPE
Alaska,I-GPE
.,O
,
Community,O
Leadership,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Professional,O
Highlights,O
:,O
Ms.,O
Sandvik,B-PERSON
is,O
president,B-TITLE
of,O
Kidways,B-ORG
LLC,I-ORG
(,O
business,O
management,O
consulting,O
),O
.,O
,
From,O
1999,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2016,I-DATE
",",O
Ms.,O
Sandvik,B-PERSON
was,O
president,B-TITLE
of,O
NANA,B-ORG
Development,I-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
(,O
NDC,B-ORG
),O
",",O
a,O
diversified,O
business,O
engaged,O
in,O
government,O
contracting,O
",",O
oilfield,O
and,O
mining,O
support,O
",",O
professional,O
management,O
services,O
",",O
and,O
engineering,O
and,O
construction,O
.,O
,
During,O
this,O
time,O
",",O
she,O
oversaw,O
the,O
growth,O
of,O
the,O
NDC,B-ORG
from,O
an,O
oil,O
field,O
support,O
services,O
company,O
with,O
revenues,O
of,O
$,B-MONEY
50,I-MONEY
million,I-MONEY
into,O
a,O
diverse,O
",",O
multi-sector,O
",",O
global,O
enterprise,O
with,O
revenues,O
of,O
$,B-MONEY
1.5,I-MONEY
billion,I-MONEY
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
that,O
",",O
Ms.,O
Sandvik,B-PERSON
served,O
in,O
a,O
variety,O
of,O
leadership,O
roles,O
within,O
the,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Department,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Transportation,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
Public,I-ORG
Facilities,I-ORG
",",O
including,O
director,B-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
statewide,I-TITLE
aviation,I-TITLE
and,O
deputy,B-TITLE
commissioner,I-TITLE
.,O
,
Ms.,O
Sandvik,B-PERSON
serves,O
on,O
the,O
board,B-ORG
of,O
the,O
National,B-ORG
Center,I-ORG
for,I-ORG
American,I-ORG
Indian,I-ORG
Enterprise,I-ORG
Development,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
non-profit,O
organization,O
.,O
,
She,O
has,O
served,O
in,O
a,O
variety,O
of,O
public,O
and,O
non-profit,O
leadership,O
roles,O
including,O
as,O
trustee,B-TITLE
to,O
the,O
Robert,B-ORG
Aqqaluk,I-ORG
Newlin,I-ORG
Trust,I-ORG
",",O
as,O
chair,B-TITLE
and,O
member,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Alaska,B-ORG
State,I-ORG
Chamber,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Commerce,I-ORG
Board,I-ORG
",",O
and,O
member,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Industrial,I-ORG
Development,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
Export,I-ORG
Authority,I-ORG
Board,I-ORG
",",O
commissioner,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
U.S.,B-ORG
Arctic,I-ORG
Research,I-ORG
Commission,I-ORG
",",O
and,O
as,O
a,O
board,B-TITLE
member,I-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Native,B-ORG
American,I-ORG
Contractors,I-ORG
Association,I-ORG
.,O
,
She,O
also,O
served,O
on,O
board,B-TITLE
of,O
the,O
Federal,B-ORG
Reserve,I-ORG
Bank,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
San,I-ORG
Francisco,I-ORG
",",O
Seattle,B-ORG
Branch,I-ORG
",",O
from,O
2004,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2009,I-DATE
and,O
was,O
its,O
chair,B-TITLE
from,O
2008,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2009,I-DATE
.,O
,
Current,O
Non-Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
and,O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
(,O
subsidiaries,O
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
),O
.,O
,
HDR,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
Education,O
:,O
BA,B-PRODUCT
",",O
Kalamazoo,B-ORG
College,I-ORG
.,O
,
MBA,B-PRODUCT
",",O
University,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Alaska,I-ORG
Fairbanks,I-ORG
.,O
,
J.,B-PERSON
Kenneth,I-PERSON
Thompson,I-PERSON
",",O
67,B-DATE
-,O
President,B-TITLE
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
",",O
Pacific,B-ORG
Star,I-ORG
Energy,I-ORG
LLC,I-ORG
.,O
,
Director,B-TITLE
since,O
1999,B-DATE
.,O
,
Compensation,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
Leadership,I-ORG
Development,I-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
.,O
,
Safety,B-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
.,O
,
Qualifications,O
:,O
Business,O
Leadership,O
Expertise,O
.,O
,
Experience,O
with,O
Strategic,O
Planning,O
",",O
Engineering,O
",",O
Operations,O
",",O
Technology,O
and,O
Research,O
",",O
and,O
Safety/Environmental/Regulatory,O
Issues,O
.,O
,
Community,O
Leadership,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Professional,O
Highlights,O
:,O
Since,O
2000,B-DATE
",",O
Mr.,O
Thompson,B-PERSON
has,O
been,O
a,O
co-owner,B-TITLE
and,O
president,B-TITLE
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Pacific,B-ORG
Star,I-ORG
Energy,I-ORG
LLC,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
firm,O
that,O
is,O
a,O
passive,O
owner,O
of,O
oil,O
lease,O
royalties,O
in,O
Alaska,B-GPE
.,O
,
He,O
served,O
from,O
2004,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2012,I-DATE
as,O
Managing,B-TITLE
Director,I-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Venture,I-ORG
Capital,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
LLC,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
private,O
oil,O
and,O
gas,O
exploration,O
firm,O
in,O
which,O
Pacific,B-ORG
Star,I-ORG
Energy,I-ORG
LLC,I-ORG
owns,O
an,O
interest,O
.,O
,
From,O
1998,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2000,I-DATE
",",O
Mr.,O
Thompson,B-PERSON
served,O
as,O
executive,B-TITLE
vice,I-TITLE
president,I-TITLE
of,O
ARCO,B-TITLE
',O
s,O
Asia,B-GPE
Pacific,I-GPE
oil,O
and,O
gas,O
operating,O
companies,O
in,O
Alaska,B-GPE
",",O
California,B-GPE
",",O
Indonesia,B-GPE
",",O
China,B-GPE
and,O
Singapore,B-GPE
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
that,O
",",O
he,O
was,O
president,B-TITLE
of,O
ARCO,B-ORG
Alaska,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
",",O
the,O
parent,O
company,O
',O
s,O
oil,O
and,O
gas,O
producing,O
division,O
based,O
in,O
Anchorage,B-GPE
",",I-GPE
Alaska,I-GPE
.,O
,
He,O
chairs,O
the,O
environmental,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
health,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
safety,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
social,I-ORG
responsibility,I-ORG
committee,I-ORG
and,O
serves,O
on,O
the,O
governance,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
nominating,I-ORG
committee,I-ORG
of,O
Coeur,B-ORG
Mining,I-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
",",O
serves,O
on,O
the,O
strategy,B-ORG
planning,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
enterprise,I-ORG
risk,I-ORG
committee,I-ORG
and,O
chairs,O
the,O
compensation,B-ORG
committee,I-ORG
at,O
Tetra,B-ORG
Tech,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
",",O
and,O
serves,O
on,O
the,O
compensation,B-ORG
committee,I-ORG
",",O
chairs,O
the,O
governance,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
nominating,I-ORG
committee,I-ORG
",",O
and,O
the,O
hydrocarbon,B-ORG
reserves,I-ORG
committee,I-ORG
",",O
as,O
well,O
as,O
serving,O
as,O
non-executive,B-TITLE
chairman,I-TITLE
of,O
the,O
board,B-ORG
of,O
Pioneer,B-ORG
Natural,I-ORG
Resources,I-ORG
Company,I-ORG
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Thompson,B-PERSON
is,O
also,O
a,O
member,B-TITLE
and,O
chair,B-TITLE
of,O
CDF,B-ORG
Capital,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
non-profit,O
organization,O
.,O
,
Current,O
Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Pioneer,B-ORG
Natural,I-ORG
Resources,I-ORG
Company,I-ORG
(,O
Non-Executive,B-TITLE
Chairman,I-TITLE
),O
.,O
,
Tetra,B-ORG
Tech,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
Coeur,B-ORG
Mining,I-ORG
Corporation,I-ORG
.,O
,
Current,O
Non-Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
and,O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
(,O
subsidiaries,O
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
),O
.,O
,
Bradley,B-PERSON
D.,I-PERSON
Tilden,I-PERSON
",",O
58,B-DATE
-,O
Chairman,B-TITLE
",",O
President,B-TITLE
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
",",O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
Chairman,B-TITLE
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
",",O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
Chairman,B-TITLE
",",O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Industries,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
Director,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
since,O
2010,B-DATE
.,O
,
Qualifications,O
:,O
Deep,O
Airline,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Strategic,O
Planning,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Financial,O
Expertise,O
.,O
,
Public,O
Company,O
CEO,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Community,O
Leadership,O
.,O
,
Professional,O
Highlights,O
:,O
Mr.,O
Tilden,B-PERSON
has,O
been,O
chairman,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
",",O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
and,O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
since,O
January,B-DATE
2014,I-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
served,O
as,O
president,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
from,O
December,B-DATE
2008,I-DATE
to,I-DATE
May,I-DATE
2016,I-DATE
.,O
,
In,O
May,B-DATE
2012,I-DATE
",",O
Mr.,O
Tilden,B-PERSON
was,O
named,O
president,B-TITLE
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
",",O
and,O
he,O
was,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
from,O
May,B-DATE
2012,I-DATE
to,I-DATE
May,I-DATE
2016,I-DATE
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
2000,B-DATE
",",O
he,O
was,O
vice,B-TITLE
president,I-TITLE
of,I-TITLE
finance,I-TITLE
at,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
and,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
.,O
,
Before,O
joining,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
",",O
Mr.,O
Tilden,B-PERSON
worked,O
for,O
the,O
accounting,O
firm,O
PricewaterhouseCoopers,B-ORG
,
.,O
Current,O
Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Nordstrom,B-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
Current,O
Non-Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
and,O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
(,O
subsidiaries,O
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
),O
.,O
,
Airlines,B-ORG
for,I-ORG
America,I-ORG
.,O
,
Boy,B-ORG
Scouts,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
America,I-ORG
.,O
,
Washington,B-ORG
Roundtable,I-ORG
.,O
,
Education,O
:,O
BA,B-PRODUCT
",",O
Pacific,B-ORG
Lutheran,I-ORG
University,I-ORG
.,O
,
MBA,B-PRODUCT
",",O
University,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Washington,I-ORG
.,O
,
Eric,B-PERSON
K.,I-PERSON
Yeaman,I-PERSON
",",O
51,B-DATE
-,O
President,B-TITLE
and,O
COO,B-TITLE
",",O
First,B-ORG
Hawaiian,I-ORG
Bank,I-ORG
.,O
,
Director,B-TITLE
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
since,O
2012,B-DATE
.,O
,
Audit,B-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
(,O
Chair,B-TITLE
),O
.,O
,
Governance,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
Nominating,I-ORG
Committee,I-ORG
.,O
,
Qualifications,O
:,O
Financial,O
Expertise,O
.,O
,
Public,O
Company,O
CEO,O
Experience,O
.,O
,
Intimate,O
Knowledge,O
of,O
the,O
Culture,O
and,O
Transportation,O
Needs,O
of,O
Hawaii,B-GPE
.,O
,
Professional,O
Highlights,O
:,O
Mr.,O
Yeaman,B-PERSON
was,O
named,O
president,B-TITLE
and,O
COO,B-TITLE
of,O
First,B-ORG
Hawaiian,I-ORG
Bank,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
wholly,O
owned,O
subsidiary,O
of,O
First,B-ORG
Hawaiian,I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
",",O
in,O
June,B-DATE
2015,I-DATE
.,O
,
From,O
2008,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2015,I-DATE
",",O
he,O
was,O
president,B-TITLE
and,O
CEO,B-TITLE
of,O
Hawaiian,B-ORG
Telcom,I-ORG
",",O
a,O
telecommunications,O
and,O
technology,O
company,O
serving,O
the,O
state,O
of,O
Hawaii,B-LOC
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
that,O
",",O
he,O
was,O
senior,B-TITLE
executive,I-TITLE
vice,I-TITLE
president,I-TITLE
and,O
COO,B-TITLE
of,O
Hawaiian,B-ORG
Electric,I-ORG
Company,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
(,O
HECO,B-ORG
),O
.,O
,
Mr.,O
Yeaman,B-PERSON
joined,O
Hawaiian,B-ORG
Electric,I-ORG
Industries,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
(,O
HEI,B-ORG
),O
",",O
HECO,B-ORG
',O
s,O
parent,O
company,O
",",O
in,O
2003,B-DATE
as,O
financial,B-TITLE
vice,I-TITLE
president,I-TITLE
",",O
treasurer,B-TITLE
and,O
CFO,B-TITLE
.,O
,
Prior,O
to,O
joining,O
HEI,B-ORG
",",O
Mr.,O
Yeaman,B-PERSON
held,O
the,O
positions,O
of,O
chief,B-TITLE
operating,I-TITLE
and,I-TITLE
financial,I-TITLE
officer,I-TITLE
for,O
Kamehameha,B-ORG
Schools,I-ORG
from,O
2000,B-DATE
to,I-DATE
2003,I-DATE
.,O
,
He,O
began,O
his,O
career,O
at,O
Arthur,B-ORG
Andersen,I-ORG
LLP,I-ORG
in,O
1989,B-DATE
.,O
,
Current,O
Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Alexander,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Baldwin,I-ORG
",",I-ORG
Inc.,I-ORG
Current,O
Non-Public,O
Company,O
Board,O
Service,O
:,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Airlines,I-ORG
and,O
Horizon,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
(,O
subsidiaries,O
of,O
Alaska,B-ORG
Air,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
),O
.,O
,
First,B-ORG
Hawaiian,I-ORG
Bank,I-ORG
.,O
,
The,B-ORG
Harold,I-ORG
K.L,I-ORG
.,O
,
Castle,B-ORG
Foundation,I-ORG
.,O
,
Hawaii,B-ORG
Asia,I-ORG
Pacific,I-ORG
Association,I-ORG
.,O
,
Education,O
:,O
BA,B-PRODUCT
",",O
University,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Hawaii,I-ORG
at,I-ORG
Manoa,I-ORG
.,O
