token	company	director	label
Jeffrey	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-PERSON
P.	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	I-PERSON
Bezos	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	I-PERSON
,	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
age	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-DATE
55	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
has	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
been	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
Chairman	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
Board	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-ORG
since	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
founding	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
Company	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-ORG
in	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
1994	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-DATE
and	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
Chief	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-TITLE
Executive	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	I-TITLE
Officer	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	I-TITLE
since	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
May	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-DATE
1996	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
			
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
Bezos	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-PERSON
served	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
President	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-TITLE
from	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
founding	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
until	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
June	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-DATE
1999	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	I-DATE
and	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
again	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
from	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
October	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-DATE
2000	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
present	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
.	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
			
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
Bezos	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-PERSON
	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
individual	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
qualifications	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-TITLE
include	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
his	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
customer-focused	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
point	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
of	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
view	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
his	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
willingness	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
to	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
encourage	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
invention	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
his	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
long-term	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
perspective	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
his	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
on-going	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
contributions	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
founder	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-TITLE
and	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
CEO	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	B-TITLE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	1.0	O
			
Rosalind	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-PERSON
G.	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-PERSON
Brewer	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-PERSON
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
age	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-DATE
56	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
has	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
been	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-TITLE
since	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
February	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-DATE
2019	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
			
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
Brewer	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-PERSON
has	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
been	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
Group	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-TITLE
President	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-TITLE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-TITLE
Americas	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-TITLE
and	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
Chief	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-TITLE
Operating	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-TITLE
Officer	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
Starbucks	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-ORG
Corporation	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
roaster	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
marketer	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
retailer	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
of	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
specialty	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
coffee	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
since	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
October	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-DATE
2017	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
where	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
she	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
has	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
also	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
served	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-TITLE
since	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
March	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-DATE
2017	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
			
From	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
February	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-DATE
2012	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
February	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
2017	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
she	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
was	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
President	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-TITLE
and	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
Chief	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-TITLE
Executive	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-TITLE
Officer	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
Sam	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-ORG
s	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-ORG
Club	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
membership-only	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
retail	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
warehouse	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
club	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
division	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
of	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
Walmart	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-ORG
Inc.	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
from	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
2006	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
January	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
2012	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
she	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
served	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
in	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
numerous	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
leadership	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
positions	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
at	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
various	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
regional	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
business	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
units	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
for	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
Walmart	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-ORG
.	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
			
She	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
served	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
Lockheed	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-ORG
Martin	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-ORG
Corporation	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
April	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-DATE
2011	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
October	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
2017	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
			
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
Brewer	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-PERSON
s	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
individual	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
qualifications	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-TITLE
include	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
leadership	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
operations	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
senior	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	B-TITLE
executive	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	I-TITLE
at	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
large	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
multinational	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
corporations	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
through	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
which	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
she	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
gained	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
with	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
regulatory	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
compliance	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
requirements	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
applicable	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
to	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
public	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
companies	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
well	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
customer	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
.	AMAZON.COM INC	2.0	O
			
Jamie	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	B-PERSON
S.	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	I-PERSON
Gorelick	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	I-PERSON
,	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
age	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	B-DATE
68	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
has	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
been	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	B-TITLE
since	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
February	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	B-DATE
2012	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
			
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
Gorelick	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	B-PERSON
has	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
been	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
partner	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
with	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
law	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
firm	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
Wilmer	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	B-ORG
Cutler	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	I-ORG
Pickering	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	I-ORG
Hale	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	I-ORG
and	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	I-ORG
Dorr	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	I-ORG
LLP	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	I-ORG
since	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
July	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	B-DATE
2003	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
			
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
Gorelick	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	B-PERSON
s	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
individual	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
qualifications	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	B-TITLE
include	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
lawyer	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	B-TITLE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
leadership	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
in	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
senior	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
governmental	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
positions	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
including	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
with	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
regulatory	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
compliance	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
matters	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
well	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
customer	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
relating	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
to	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
public	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
policy	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
financial	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
statement	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
accounting	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
matters	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
.	AMAZON.COM INC	3.0	O
			
Judith	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-PERSON
A.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-PERSON
McGrath	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-PERSON
,	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
age	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-DATE
66	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
has	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
been	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-TITLE
since	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
July	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-DATE
2014	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
			
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
McGrath	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-PERSON
serves	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
senior	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-TITLE
advisor	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-TITLE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
Astronauts	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-ORG
Wanted	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
*	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
No	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
necessary	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
multimedia	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
joint	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
venture	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
that	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
McGrath	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-PERSON
formed	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
with	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
Sony	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-ORG
Music	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
Entertainment	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
served	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
President	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
Astronauts	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-ORG
Wanted	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
June	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-DATE
2013	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-DATE
March	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-DATE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-DATE
2018	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
			
The	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
company	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
is	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
currently	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
subsidiary	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
of	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
Sony	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-ORG
Pictures	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
Television	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
			
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
McGrath	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-PERSON
served	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
Chair	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-TITLE
and	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
Chief	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-TITLE
Executive	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-TITLE
Officer	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
MTV	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-ORG
Networks	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
Entertainment	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
Group	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
worldwide	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
division	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
of	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
Viacom	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
Inc.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
including	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
Comedy	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-ORG
Central	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
and	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
Nickelodeon	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
from	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
July	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-DATE
2004	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-DATE
until	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-DATE
May	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-DATE
2011	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
			
She	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
was	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
part	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
of	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
original	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
founder	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
launch	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
team	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
for	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
MTV	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-ORG
.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
			
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
McGrath	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-PERSON
s	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
individual	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
qualifications	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-TITLE
include	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
leadership	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
multimedia	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
operations	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
longtime	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
senior	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-TITLE
executive	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
MTV	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-ORG
Networks	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
Entertainment	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
Group	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
through	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
which	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
she	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
gained	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
with	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
content	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
creation	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
advertising	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
content	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
distribution	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
well	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
customer	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
			
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
McGrath	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-PERSON
further	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
honed	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
digital	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
entrepreneurial	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
with	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
global	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
customers	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
in	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
role	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
at	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
Astronauts	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	B-ORG
Wanted	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
*	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
No	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
necessary	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	I-ORG
.	AMAZON.COM INC	4.0	O
			
Indra	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-PERSON
K.	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-PERSON
Nooyi	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-PERSON
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
age	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-DATE
63	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
has	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
been	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-TITLE
since	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
February	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-DATE
2019	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
			
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
Nooyi	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-PERSON
was	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
Chief	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-TITLE
Executive	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-TITLE
Officer	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
PepsiCo	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-ORG
Inc.	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
multinational	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
food	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
snack	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
beverage	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
company	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
from	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
October	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-DATE
2006	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-DATE
October	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-DATE
2018	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
where	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
she	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
also	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
served	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
Chairman	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
its	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
board	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-ORG
of	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-ORG
directors	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
May	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-DATE
2007	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-DATE
February	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-DATE
2019	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
			
She	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
was	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
elected	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
to	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
PepsiCo	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-ORG
s	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
board	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-ORG
of	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-ORG
directors	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-ORG
and	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
became	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
its	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
President	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-TITLE
and	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
Chief	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-TITLE
Financial	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-TITLE
Officer	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-TITLE
in	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
2001	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
held	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
leadership	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
roles	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
in	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
finance	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
corporate	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
strategy	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
development	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
strategic	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
planning	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
after	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
joining	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
PepsiCo	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-ORG
in	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
1994	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
			
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
Nooyi	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-PERSON
has	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
served	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
Schlumberger	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-ORG
Limited	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-ORG
since	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
April	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-DATE
2015	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
			
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
Nooyi	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-PERSON
s	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
individual	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
qualifications	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-TITLE
include	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
leadership	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
longtime	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
senior	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	B-TITLE
executive	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	I-TITLE
at	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
large	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
corporation	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
with	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
international	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
operations	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
through	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
which	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
she	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
gained	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
with	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
consumer-focused	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
product	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
development	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
international	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
operations	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
marketing	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
issues	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
well	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
customer	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
relating	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
to	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
financial	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
statement	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
accounting	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
matters	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
.	AMAZON.COM INC	5.0	O
			
Jonathan	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-PERSON
J.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-PERSON
Rubinstein	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-PERSON
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
age	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-DATE
62	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
has	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
been	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-TITLE
since	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
December	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-DATE
2010	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
			
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Rubinstein	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-PERSON
was	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
co-CEO	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Bridgewater	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
Associates	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
LP	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
global	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
investment	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
management	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
firm	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
from	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
May	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-DATE
2016	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
April	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
2017	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
			
Previously	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Rubinstein	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-PERSON
was	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Senior	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-TITLE
Vice	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-TITLE
President	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-TITLE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-TITLE
Product	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-TITLE
Innovation	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-TITLE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
for	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Personal	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
Systems	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
Group	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
at	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Hewlett-Packard	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
Company	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
(	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
“	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
HP	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
”	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
)	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
multinational	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
information	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
technology	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
company	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
from	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
July	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-DATE
2011	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
January	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
2012	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
served	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Senior	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-PERSON
Vice	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-PERSON
President	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-PERSON
and	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
General	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-PERSON
Manager	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-PERSON
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Palm	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
Global	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
Business	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
Unit	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
at	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
HP	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
July	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-DATE
2010	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
July	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
2011	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
			
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Rubinstein	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-PERSON
was	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Chief	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-TITLE
Executive	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-TITLE
Officer	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-TITLE
and	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
President	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Palm	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
Inc.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
smartphone	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
manufacturer	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
from	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
June	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-DATE
2009	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
until	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
its	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
acquisition	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
by	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
HP	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
in	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
July	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-DATE
2010	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Chairman	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Board	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
of	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Palm	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
Inc.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
October	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-DATE
2007	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
through	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
acquisition	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
			
Prior	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
to	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
joining	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Palm	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Rubinstein	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-PERSON
was	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Senior	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-TITLE
Vice	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-TITLE
President	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-TITLE
at	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Apple	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
Inc.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
also	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
serving	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
General	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-TITLE
Manager	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
iPod	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
Division	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
			
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Rubinstein	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-PERSON
served	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Qualcomm	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-ORG
Incorporated	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
May	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-DATE
2013	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
May	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
2016	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
			
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
Rubinstein	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-PERSON
s	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
individual	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
qualifications	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-TITLE
include	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
his	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
leadership	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
technology	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
senior	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	B-TITLE
executive	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	I-TITLE
at	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
large	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
financial	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
technology	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
companies	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
through	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
which	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
he	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
gained	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
with	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
hardware	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
devices	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
emerging	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
technologies	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
well	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
his	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
customer	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
relating	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
to	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
financial	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
statement	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
accounting	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
matters	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
.	AMAZON.COM INC	6.0	O
			
Thomas	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-PERSON
O.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-PERSON
Ryder	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-PERSON
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
age	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-DATE
74	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
has	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
been	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-TITLE
since	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
November	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-DATE
2002	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
			
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Ryder	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-PERSON
was	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Chairman	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Reader	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-ORG
s	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Digest	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Association	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Inc.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
April	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-DATE
1998	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
December	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
2006	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
was	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Chief	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-TITLE
Executive	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-TITLE
Officer	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-TITLE
from	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
April	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-DATE
1998	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
December	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
2005	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
			
From	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
1984	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
1998	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Ryder	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-PERSON
worked	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
in	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
several	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
roles	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
at	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
American	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-ORG
Express	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
including	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
President	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
American	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-ORG
Express	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Travel	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Related	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Services	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
International	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
			
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Ryder	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-PERSON
served	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
ILG	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Inc.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
May	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-DATE
2016	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
September	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
2018	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
RPX	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-ORG
Corporation	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
December	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-DATE
2009	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
June	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
2017	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Quad/Graphics	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Inc.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
July	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-DATE
2010	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
May	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
2017	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Starwood	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-ORG
Hotels	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
&	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Resorts	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Worldwide	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Inc.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
April	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-DATE
2001	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
September	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
2016	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Chairman	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Board	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-ORG
of	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Directors	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
at	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Virgin	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-ORG
Mobile	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
USA	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Inc.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
October	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-DATE
2007	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
November	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
2009	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
			
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Ryder	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-PERSON
s	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
individual	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
qualifications	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-TITLE
include	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
his	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
leadership	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
senior	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
executive	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
of	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
Reader	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-ORG
s	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
Digest	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
large	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
media	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
publishing	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
company	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
American	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	B-ORG
Express	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
large	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
financial	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
services	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
company	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
through	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
which	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
he	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
gained	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
with	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
intellectual	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
property	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
media	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
enterprise	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
sales	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
payments	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
international	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
operations	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
well	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
his	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
customer	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
relating	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
to	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
financial	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
statement	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
accounting	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
matters	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
.	AMAZON.COM INC	7.0	O
			
Patricia	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-PERSON
Q.	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-PERSON
Stonesifer	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-PERSON
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
age	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
62	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
has	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
been	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-TITLE
since	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
February	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
1997	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
			
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Stonesifer	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-PERSON
served	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
President	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-TITLE
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
CEO	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Martha	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-ORG
s	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
Table	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
non-profit	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
from	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
April	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
2013	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
March	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
2019	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
			
She	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
served	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Chair	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Board	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-ORG
of	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
Regents	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
of	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Smithsonian	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-ORG
Institution	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
January	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
2009	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
January	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
2012	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Vice	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-TITLE
Chair	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-TITLE
from	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
January	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
2012	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
January	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
2013	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
			
From	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
September	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
2008	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
January	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
2012	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
she	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
served	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
senior	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-TITLE
advisor	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-TITLE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Bill	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-ORG
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
Melinda	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
Gates	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
Foundation	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
private	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
philanthropic	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
organization	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
where	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
she	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
was	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Chief	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-TITLE
Executive	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-TITLE
Officer	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-TITLE
from	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
January	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
2006	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
September	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
2008	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
President	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-PERSON
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Co-chair	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-PERSON
from	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
June	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
1997	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
January	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
2006	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
			
Since	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
September	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
2009	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
she	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
has	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
also	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
served	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
private	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
philanthropy	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
advisor	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
.	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
			
From	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
1988	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
1997	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
she	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
worked	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
in	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
many	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
roles	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
at	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Microsoft	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-ORG
Corporation	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
including	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Senior	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-TITLE
Vice	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-TITLE
President	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Interactive	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-ORG
Media	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
Division	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
also	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
served	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Chairwoman	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Gates	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-ORG
Learning	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
Foundation	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
1997	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
to	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-DATE
1999	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
			
Ms.	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Stonesifer	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-PERSON
s	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
individual	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
qualifications	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-TITLE
include	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
leadership	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
senior	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
executive	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
at	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Bill	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-ORG
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
Melinda	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
Gates	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
Foundation	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	I-ORG
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
at	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Microsoft	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
through	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
which	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
she	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
gained	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
with	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
emerging	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
technologies	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
consumer	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
-	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
focused	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
product	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
development	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
marketing	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
issues	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
knowledge	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
of	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
Amazon	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-ORG
from	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
having	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
served	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-TITLE
since	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
1997	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	B-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
well	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
her	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
customer	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
relating	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
to	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
public	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
policy	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
financial	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
statement	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
accounting	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
matters	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
.	AMAZON.COM INC	8.0	O
			
Wendell	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-PERSON
P.	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-PERSON
Weeks	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-PERSON
,	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
age	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-DATE
59	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-DATE
,	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
has	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
been	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-TITLE
since	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
February	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-DATE
2016	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
			
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
Weeks	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-PERSON
has	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
been	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
Chief	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-TITLE
Executive	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-TITLE
Officer	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
Corning	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-ORG
Incorporated	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
glass	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
materials	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
science	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
innovator	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
since	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
April	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-DATE
2005	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-DATE
;	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
Chairman	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
board	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-ORG
of	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-ORG
directors	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-ORG
since	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
April	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-DATE
2007	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-DATE
;	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
President	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-TITLE
since	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
December	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-DATE
2010	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
			
He	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
has	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
held	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
leadership	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
roles	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
in	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
financial	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
management	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
business	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
development	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
commercial	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
leadership	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
general	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
management	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
across	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
many	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
of	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
Corning	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-ORG
s	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
businesses	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
technologies	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
since	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
joining	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
the	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
company	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
in	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
1983	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
			
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
Weeks	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-PERSON
has	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
served	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-TITLE
of	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
Merck	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-ORG
&	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-ORG
Co.	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-ORG
,	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-ORG
Inc.	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-ORG
since	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
February	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-DATE
2004	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	I-DATE
.	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
			
Mr.	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
Weeks	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	B-PERSON
	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
individual	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
qualifications	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
director	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
include	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
his	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
leadership	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
operations	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
senior	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
executive	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
at	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
a	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
large	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
corporation	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
with	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
international	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
operations	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
with	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
product	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
development	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
,	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
well	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
as	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
his	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
customer	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
experience	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
skills	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
relating	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
to	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
financial	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
statement	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
and	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
accounting	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
matters	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
.	AMAZON.COM INC	9.0	O
			
WARREN	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-PERSON
E.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-PERSON
BUFFETT	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-PERSON
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
age	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-DATE
88	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-TITLE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
controlling	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-TITLE
shareholder	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-ORG
since	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
1965	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-DATE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
its	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
Chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-TITLE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
Chief	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-TITLE
Executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-TITLE
Officer	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-TITLE
since	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
1970	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
			
Mr.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
Buffett	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-PERSON
was	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
The	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-ORG
Kraft	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-ORG
Heinz	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-ORG
Company	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-ORG
until	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
April	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-DATE
2018	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
			
Additional	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
Qualifications	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
:	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
Warren	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-PERSON
Buffett	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-PERSON
brings	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
Board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-ORG
his	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
49	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-DATE
years	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-DATE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
experience	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
Chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-TITLE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
Chief	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-TITLE
Executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-TITLE
Officer	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	I-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	B-ORG
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	10.0	O
			
GREGORY	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-PERSON
E.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-PERSON
ABEL	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-PERSON
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
age	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-DATE
56	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
was	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
elected	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-ORG
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-ORG
s	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Vice	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-TITLE
Chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-TITLE
–	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-TITLE
Non	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-TITLE
Insurance	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-TITLE
Operations	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-TITLE
on	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
January	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-DATE
9	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-DATE
2018	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
			
Between	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
2008	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-DATE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-DATE
January	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-DATE
9	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-DATE
2018	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Mr.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Abel	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-PERSON
served	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Chief	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-TITLE
Executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-TITLE
Officer	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Berkshire	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-ORG
Hathaway	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-ORG
Energy	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-ORG
Company	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-ORG
(	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
“	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
BHE	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-ORG
”	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
)	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
90.9	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-PERCENT
%	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-PERCENT
owned	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
subsidiary	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Berkshire	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-ORG
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
			
In	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
2011	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Mr.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Abel	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-PERSON
was	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
elected	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
BHE	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-ORG
s	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-TITLE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
was	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
elected	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
its	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-TITLE
Chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-TITLE
on	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
January	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-DATE
10	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-DATE
2018	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
			
Mr.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Abel	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-PERSON
also	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
serves	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
The	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-ORG
Kraft	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-ORG
Heinz	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-ORG
Company	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-ORG
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
AEGIS	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-ORG
Insurance	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-ORG
Services	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-ORG
Inc.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
provider	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
property	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
liability	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
insurance	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
for	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
energy	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
industry	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
			
Additional	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Qualifications	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
:	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Gregory	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-PERSON
Abel	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-PERSON
brings	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
Board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-ORG
his	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
26	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-DATE
years	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-DATE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
experience	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
in	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
various	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
positions	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
at	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
BHE	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
including	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
serving	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
its	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
CEO	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-TITLE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
			
He	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
also	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
brings	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-ORG
his	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
experience	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
The	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	B-ORG
Kraft	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-ORG
Heinz	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-ORG
Company	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	I-ORG
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	11.0	O
			
HOWARD	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-PERSON
G.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-PERSON
BUFFETT	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-PERSON
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
age	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-DATE
64	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-ORG
since	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
1993	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
			
Mr.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Buffett	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-PERSON
is	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
currently	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Undersheriff	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Macon	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-GPE
County	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-GPE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Illinois	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-GPE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
was	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
its	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Sheriff	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-TITLE
between	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
September	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-DATE
2017	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-DATE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-DATE
December	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-DATE
2018	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
			
Since	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
2013	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Mr.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Buffett	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-PERSON
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-TITLE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Chief	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-TITLE
Executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-TITLE
Officer	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Howard	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-ORG
G.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-ORG
Buffett	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-ORG
Foundation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
charitable	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
foundation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
that	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
directs	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
funding	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
for	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
humanitarian	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
conservation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
related	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
issues	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
			
Between	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
1999	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-DATE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-DATE
2013	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
he	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
served	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
President	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Howard	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-ORG
G.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-ORG
Buffett	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-ORG
Foundation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-ORG
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
			
He	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
was	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
The	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-ORG
Coca-Cola	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-ORG
Company	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-ORG
until	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
April	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-DATE
2017	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Lindsay	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-ORG
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-ORG
until	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
January	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-DATE
2016	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-DATE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Sloan	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-ORG
Implement	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-ORG
Company	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-ORG
until	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
May	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-DATE
2015	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
			
Additional	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Qualifications	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
:	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Howard	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-PERSON
Buffett	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	I-PERSON
brings	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-ORG
his	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
experience	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
owner	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
small	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
business	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
past	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
senior	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
public	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
public	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
corporations	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
Chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-TITLE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
CEO	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
large	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
charitable	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
foundation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	12.0	O
			
STEPHEN	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-PERSON
B.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-PERSON
BURKE	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-PERSON
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
age	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-DATE
60	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-ORG
since	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
2009	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
			
Mr.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
Burke	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-PERSON
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
Chief	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-TITLE
Executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-TITLE
Officer	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
NBCUniversal	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-ORG
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
Senior	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-TITLE
Executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-TITLE
Vice	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-TITLE
President	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
Comcast	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-ORG
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-ORG
since	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
January	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-DATE
2011	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
			
Prior	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
that	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
time	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
from	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
2004	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-DATE
until	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-DATE
January	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-DATE
2011	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
he	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
was	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
Chief	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-TITLE
Operating	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-TITLE
Officer	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
Comcast	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-ORG
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
President	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
Comcast	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-ORG
Cable	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-ORG
Communications	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-ORG
from	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
1998	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-DATE
until	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-DATE
January	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-DATE
2010	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
			
He	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
is	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
also	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
JPMorgan	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-ORG
Chase	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-ORG
&	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-ORG
Co.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-ORG
Additional	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
Qualifications	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
:	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
Stephen	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-PERSON
Burke	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	I-PERSON
brings	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
Board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	B-ORG
his	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
experience	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
senior	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
public	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
his	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
financial	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
expertise	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
major	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
banking	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
institution	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	13.0	O
			
SUSAN	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-PERSON
L.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-PERSON
DECKER	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-PERSON
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
age	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-DATE
56	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
since	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
2007	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
			
Ms.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Decker	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-PERSON
also	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
serves	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
on	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
boards	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
directors	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Costco	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
Wholesale	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Vail	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
Resorts	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
Inc.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
SurveyMonkey	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Vox	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
Media	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
			
She	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
is	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
CEO	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-TITLE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Founder	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Raftr	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
incorporated	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
in	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
2018	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-DATE
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
an	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
authenticated	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
private	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
social	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
network	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
for	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
university	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
students	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
administrations	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
			
From	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
June	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-DATE
2000	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
April	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
2009	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Ms.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Decker	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-PERSON
held	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
various	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
management	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
positions	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
at	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Yahoo	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
!	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
Inc.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
global	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Internet	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
brand	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
including	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
President	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-TITLE
(	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
June	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-DATE
2007	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
April	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
2009	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
)	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
head	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Advertiser	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
Publisher	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
Group	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
(	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
December	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-DATE
2006	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
June	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
2007	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
)	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Chief	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-TITLE
Financial	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-TITLE
Officer	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-TITLE
(	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
June	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-DATE
2000	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
June	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
2007	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
)	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
			
Before	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Yahoo	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
!	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Ms.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Decker	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-PERSON
spent	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
14	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-DATE
years	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
with	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Donaldson	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
Lufkin	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
&	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
Jenrette	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
			
She	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
is	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Chartered	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-TITLE
Financial	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-TITLE
Analyst	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-TITLE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
served	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
on	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Financial	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
Accounting	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
Standards	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
Advisory	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
Council	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
for	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
four-year	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-DATE
term	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
from	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
2000	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-DATE
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
2004	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
			
Additional	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Qualifications	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
:	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Susan	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-PERSON
Decker	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-PERSON
brings	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
her	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
experience	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
past	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
senior	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
public	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
public	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
corporations	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
her	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
financial	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
expertise	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
former	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
equity	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
securities	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
analyst	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
former	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
member	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
Financial	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	B-ORG
Accounting	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
Standards	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
Advisory	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
Council	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	I-ORG
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	14.0	O
			
WILLIAM	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-PERSON
H.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-PERSON
GATES	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-PERSON
III	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-PERSON
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
age	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-DATE
63	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-ORG
since	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
2005	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
			
Mr.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Gates	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
currently	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
serves	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Co-Chair	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Bill	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-ORG
&	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-ORG
Melinda	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-ORG
Gates	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-ORG
Foundation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-ORG
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
			
Mr.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Gates	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-PERSON
is	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Microsoft	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-ORG
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-ORG
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
served	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-ORG
from	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
its	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
incorporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
in	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
1981	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-DATE
until	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-DATE
February	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-DATE
2014	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
			
Mr.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Gates	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-PERSON
is	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
currently	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Technology	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-TITLE
Advisor	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-TITLE
for	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Microsoft	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-ORG
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-ORG
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
was	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
its	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Chief	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-TITLE
Executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-TITLE
Officer	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-TITLE
from	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
1981	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-DATE
until	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-DATE
January	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-DATE
2000	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
			
Additional	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Qualifications	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
:	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
William	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-PERSON
Gates	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-PERSON
brings	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-ORG
his	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
experience	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
financial	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
expertise	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
past	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-ORG
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-ORG
directors	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-ORG
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
chief	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-TITLE
executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-TITLE
officer	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	I-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
public	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
Co-Chair	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
major	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
charitable	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
foundation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	15.0	O
			
DAVID	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	B-PERSON
S.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	I-PERSON
GOTTESMAN	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	I-PERSON
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
age	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	B-DATE
92	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	B-ORG
since	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
2004	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	B-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
			
For	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
more	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
than	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
past	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
five	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	B-DATE
years	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
he	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
principal	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
First	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	B-ORG
Manhattan	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	I-ORG
Co.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
an	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
investment	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
advisory	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
firm	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
			
Additional	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
Qualifications	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
:	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
David	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	B-PERSON
Gottesman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	I-PERSON
brings	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
Board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	B-ORG
his	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
experience	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
financial	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
expertise	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
principal	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
private	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
investment	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
manager	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	16.0	O
			
CHARLOTTE	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-PERSON
GUYMAN	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	I-PERSON
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
age	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-DATE
62	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-ORG
since	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
2003	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
			
Ms.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
Guyman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-PERSON
is	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
co-founder	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
BoardReady	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
not	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
for	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
profit	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
whose	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
mission	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
is	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
catapult	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
diversification	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
through	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
data	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
experience	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
network	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
strategies	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
			
Ms.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
Guyman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-PERSON
is	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
currently	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
strategic	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
advisor	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
Cameoworks	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
global	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
retail	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
financial	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
services	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
advisory	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
firm	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
			
She	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
was	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
general	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-TITLE
manager	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	I-TITLE
with	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
Microsoft	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-ORG
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	I-ORG
until	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
July	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-DATE
1999	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	I-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
			
She	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
is	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
Space	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-ORG
Needle	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	I-ORG
LLC	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	I-ORG
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
Pro.com	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
trustee	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
Save	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-ORG
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	I-ORG
Children	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	I-ORG
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
was	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
former	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
Chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
Board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-ORG
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	I-ORG
Directors	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	I-ORG
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
UW	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-ORG
Medicine	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
an	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
academic	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
medical	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
center	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
			
Additional	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
Qualifications	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
:	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
Charlotte	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-PERSON
Guyman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	I-PERSON
brings	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
Board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	B-ORG
her	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
experience	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
past	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
senior	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
public	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
her	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
financial	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
expertise	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
former	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
major	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
academic	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
medical	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
center	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	17.0	O
			
AJIT	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-PERSON
JAIN	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-PERSON
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
age	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-DATE
67	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
was	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
elected	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-ORG
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
its	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Vice	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-TITLE
Chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-TITLE
–	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-TITLE
Insurance	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-TITLE
Operations	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-TITLE
on	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
January	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-DATE
9	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-DATE
2018	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
			
Mr.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Jain	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-PERSON
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
employed	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
by	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Berkshire	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-ORG
Hathaway	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-ORG
Insurance	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-ORG
Group	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-ORG
since	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
1986	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
an	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-TITLE
Vice	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-TITLE
President	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
National	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-ORG
Indemnity	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-ORG
Company	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
wholly	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
owned	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Berkshire	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-ORG
subsidiary	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
since	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
1996	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
			
Mr.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Jain	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-PERSON
is	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Trustee	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Rockefeller	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-ORG
University	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
leading	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
biomedical	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
research	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
university	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
			
Additional	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Qualifications	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
:	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Ajit	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-PERSON
Jain	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-PERSON
brings	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
to	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-ORG
his	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
32	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-DATE
years	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	I-DATE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
experience	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
in	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
managing	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Berkshire	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-ORG
s	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
reinsurance	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
operations	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
one	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
its	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
most	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
important	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
businesses	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
			
During	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
this	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
period	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
he	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
responsible	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
for	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
overseeing	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
assessment	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
pricing	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
many	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
largest	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
most	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
complex	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
risks	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
ever	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
insured	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
as	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
result	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
generating	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
billions	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
dollars	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
capital	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
for	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
deployment	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
by	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	B-ORG
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	18.0	O
			
CHARLES	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-PERSON
T.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-PERSON
MUNGER	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-PERSON
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
age	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-DATE
95	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
has	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
been	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
a	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
director	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-TITLE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
Vice	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-TITLE
Chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-ORG
s	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
Board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-ORG
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-ORG
Directors	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-ORG
since	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
1978	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-DATE
.	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
			
Between	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
1984	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-DATE
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-DATE
2011	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-DATE
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
he	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
was	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
Chairman	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
Board	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-ORG
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-ORG
Directors	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-ORG
and	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
Chief	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-TITLE
Executive	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-TITLE
Officer	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-TITLE
of	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
Wesco	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-ORG
Financial	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-ORG
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-ORG
,	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
approximately	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
80	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-PERCENT
%	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	I-PERCENT
-owned	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
by	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
the	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
Corporation	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	B-ORG
during	BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY INC-CL B	19.0	O
